{
    "sample_0": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Tasmanian Legislative Council .",
        "sentence": "The Electoral division of Apsley is one of the 15 electorates or seats in the Tasmanian Legislative Council ."
    },
    "sample_1": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "second-largest upper house electorate",
        "sentence": "It is the second-largest upper house electorate in the state by area after Murchison ."
    },
    "sample_2": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "after Murchison .",
        "sentence": "It is the second-largest upper house electorate in the state by area after Murchison ."
    },
    "sample_3": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": Pipers River ,",
        "sentence": "Towns within the division include : Pipers River , Scottsdale , Evandale , Swansea , Derby , Lilydale , Bridport , Campbell Town , , St Helens , Branxholm ,"
    },
    "sample_4": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Scottsdale ,",
        "sentence": "Towns within the division include : Pipers River , Scottsdale , Evandale , Swansea , Derby , Lilydale , Bridport , Campbell Town , , St Helens , Branxholm ,"
    },
    "sample_5": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Evandale ,",
        "sentence": "Towns within the division include : Pipers River , Scottsdale , Evandale , Swansea , Derby , Lilydale , Bridport , Campbell Town , , St Helens , Branxholm ,"
    },
    "sample_6": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Swansea ,",
        "sentence": "Towns within the division include : Pipers River , Scottsdale , Evandale , Swansea , Derby , Lilydale , Bridport , Campbell Town , , St Helens , Branxholm ,"
    },
    "sample_7": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Derby ,",
        "sentence": "Towns within the division include : Pipers River , Scottsdale , Evandale , Swansea , Derby , Lilydale , Bridport , Campbell Town , , St Helens , Branxholm ,"
    },
    "sample_8": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Lilydale ,",
        "sentence": "Towns within the division include : Pipers River , Scottsdale , Evandale , Swansea , Derby , Lilydale , Bridport , Campbell Town , , St Helens , Branxholm ,"
    },
    "sample_9": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Bridport ,",
        "sentence": "Towns within the division include : Pipers River , Scottsdale , Evandale , Swansea , Derby , Lilydale , Bridport , Campbell Town , , St Helens , Branxholm ,"
    },
    "sample_10": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Campbell Town ,",
        "sentence": "Towns within the division include : Pipers River , Scottsdale , Evandale , Swansea , Derby , Lilydale , Bridport , Campbell Town , , St Helens , Branxholm ,"
    },
    "sample_11": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", St Helens ,",
        "sentence": "Towns within the division include : Pipers River , Scottsdale , Evandale , Swansea , Derby , Lilydale , Bridport , Campbell Town , , St Helens , Branxholm ,"
    },
    "sample_12": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Branxholm ,",
        "sentence": "Towns within the division include : Pipers River , Scottsdale , Evandale , Swansea , Derby , Lilydale , Bridport , Campbell Town , , St Helens , Branxholm ,"
    },
    "sample_13": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Avoca ,",
        "sentence": "Towns within the division include : Pipers River , Scottsdale , Evandale , Swansea , Derby , Lilydale , Bridport , Campbell Town , , St Helens , Branxholm ,"
    },
    "sample_14": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Fingal ,",
        "sentence": "Towns within the division include : Pipers River , Scottsdale , Evandale , Swansea , Derby , Lilydale , Bridport , Campbell Town , , St Helens , Branxholm ,"
    },
    "sample_15": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Bicheno ,",
        "sentence": "Towns within the division include : Pipers River , Scottsdale , Evandale , Swansea , Derby , Lilydale , Bridport , Campbell Town , , St Helens , Branxholm ,"
    },
    "sample_16": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Bagdad ,",
        "sentence": "Towns within the division include : Pipers River , Scottsdale , Evandale , Swansea , Derby , Lilydale , Bridport , Campbell Town , , St Helens , Branxholm ,"
    },
    "sample_17": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Bellingham ,",
        "sentence": "Towns within the division include : Pipers River , Scottsdale , Evandale , Swansea , Derby , Lilydale , Bridport , Campbell Town , , St Helens , Branxholm ,"
    },
    "sample_18": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Tomahawk ,",
        "sentence": "Towns within the division include : Pipers River , Scottsdale , Evandale , Swansea , Derby , Lilydale , Bridport , Campbell Town , , St Helens , Branxholm ,"
    },
    "sample_19": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Ross ,",
        "sentence": "Towns within the division include : Pipers River , Scottsdale , Evandale , Swansea , Derby , Lilydale , Bridport , Campbell Town , , St Helens , Branxholm ,"
    },
    "sample_20": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", St Marys ,",
        "sentence": "Towns within the division include : Pipers River , Scottsdale , Evandale , Swansea , Derby , Lilydale , Bridport , Campbell Town , , St Helens , Branxholm ,"
    },
    "sample_21": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", <UNK> <UNK>",
        "sentence": "Towns within the division include : Pipers River , Scottsdale , Evandale , Swansea , Derby , Lilydale , Bridport , Campbell Town , , St Helens , Branxholm ,"
    },
    "sample_22": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "an tributary of",
        "sentence": "The Big Blue River is an tributary of the Driftwood River in east-central Indiana in the United States ."
    },
    "sample_23": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Driftwood River in",
        "sentence": "The Big Blue River is an tributary of the Driftwood River in east-central Indiana in the United States ."
    },
    "sample_24": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "east-central Indiana in",
        "sentence": "The Big Blue River is an tributary of the Driftwood River in east-central Indiana in the United States ."
    },
    "sample_25": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the United States .",
        "sentence": "The Big Blue River is an tributary of the Driftwood River in east-central Indiana in the United States ."
    },
    "sample_26": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", White ,",
        "sentence": "Via the Driftwood , White , Wabash and Ohio rivers , it is part of the watershed of the Mississippi River ."
    },
    "sample_27": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Wabash and",
        "sentence": "Via the Driftwood , White , Wabash and Ohio rivers , it is part of the watershed of the Mississippi River ."
    },
    "sample_28": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Ohio rivers",
        "sentence": "Via the Driftwood , White , Wabash and Ohio rivers , it is part of the watershed of the Mississippi River ."
    },
    "sample_29": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the watershed of",
        "sentence": "Via the Driftwood , White , Wabash and Ohio rivers , it is part of the watershed of the Mississippi River ."
    },
    "sample_30": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Mississippi River .",
        "sentence": "Via the Driftwood , White , Wabash and Ohio rivers , it is part of the watershed of the Mississippi River ."
    },
    "sample_31": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "northeastern Henry County and",
        "sentence": "The Big Blue rises in northeastern Henry County and flows generally <UNK> through Rush , Hancock , Shelby and Johnson counties , past the towns of New Castle , Knightstown"
    },
    "sample_32": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "through Rush ,",
        "sentence": "The Big Blue rises in northeastern Henry County and flows generally <UNK> through Rush , Hancock , Shelby and Johnson counties , past the towns of New Castle , Knightstown"
    },
    "sample_33": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Hancock ,",
        "sentence": "The Big Blue rises in northeastern Henry County and flows generally <UNK> through Rush , Hancock , Shelby and Johnson counties , past the towns of New Castle , Knightstown"
    },
    "sample_34": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Shelby and",
        "sentence": "The Big Blue rises in northeastern Henry County and flows generally <UNK> through Rush , Hancock , Shelby and Johnson counties , past the towns of New Castle , Knightstown"
    },
    "sample_35": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Johnson counties",
        "sentence": "The Big Blue rises in northeastern Henry County and flows generally <UNK> through Rush , Hancock , Shelby and Johnson counties , past the towns of New Castle , Knightstown"
    },
    "sample_36": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of New Castle ,",
        "sentence": "The Big Blue rises in northeastern Henry County and flows generally <UNK> through Rush , Hancock , Shelby and Johnson counties , past the towns of New Castle , Knightstown"
    },
    "sample_37": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Knightstown ,",
        "sentence": "The Big Blue rises in northeastern Henry County and flows generally <UNK> through Rush , Hancock , Shelby and Johnson counties , past the towns of New Castle , Knightstown"
    },
    "sample_38": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Carthage ,",
        "sentence": "The Big Blue rises in northeastern Henry County and flows generally <UNK> through Rush , Hancock , Shelby and Johnson counties , past the towns of New Castle , Knightstown"
    },
    "sample_39": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Morristown ,",
        "sentence": "The Big Blue rises in northeastern Henry County and flows generally <UNK> through Rush , Hancock , Shelby and Johnson counties , past the towns of New Castle , Knightstown"
    },
    "sample_40": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Shelbyville and",
        "sentence": "The Big Blue rises in northeastern Henry County and flows generally <UNK> through Rush , Hancock , Shelby and Johnson counties , past the towns of New Castle , Knightstown"
    },
    "sample_41": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Edinburgh .",
        "sentence": "The Big Blue rises in northeastern Henry County and flows generally <UNK> through Rush , Hancock , Shelby and Johnson counties , past the towns of New Castle , Knightstown"
    },
    "sample_42": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "joins Sugar Creek to",
        "sentence": "It joins Sugar Creek to form the Driftwood River west of Edinburgh ."
    },
    "sample_43": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "an Austria n",
        "sentence": "Markus Prock ( born 22 June 1964 ) is an Austria n luge r who competed between 1983 and 2002 ."
    },
    "sample_44": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "n luge r",
        "sentence": "Markus Prock ( born 22 June 1964 ) is an Austria n luge r who competed between 1983 and 2002 ."
    },
    "sample_45": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Innsbruck ,",
        "sentence": "Born in Innsbruck , Prock competed in six winning three medals in the men 's singles event with two silvers ( 1992 , 1994 ) and one bronze ( 2002"
    },
    "sample_46": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "( 1992 ,",
        "sentence": "Born in Innsbruck , Prock competed in six winning three medals in the men 's singles event with two silvers ( 1992 , 1994 ) and one bronze ( 2002"
    },
    "sample_47": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 1994 )",
        "sentence": "Born in Innsbruck , Prock competed in six winning three medals in the men 's singles event with two silvers ( 1992 , 1994 ) and one bronze ( 2002"
    },
    "sample_48": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "( 2002 )",
        "sentence": "Born in Innsbruck , Prock competed in six winning three medals in the men 's singles event with two silvers ( 1992 , 1994 ) and one bronze ( 2002"
    },
    "sample_49": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the FIL World Luge Championships ,",
        "sentence": "At the FIL World Luge Championships , Prock won 13 medals , including five gold ( Men 's singles : 1987 , 1996 ; Mixed team : 1996 , 1997"
    },
    "sample_50": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": 1987 ,",
        "sentence": "At the FIL World Luge Championships , Prock won 13 medals , including five gold ( Men 's singles : 1987 , 1996 ; Mixed team : 1996 , 1997"
    },
    "sample_51": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 1996 ;",
        "sentence": "At the FIL World Luge Championships , Prock won 13 medals , including five gold ( Men 's singles : 1987 , 1996 ; Mixed team : 1996 , 1997"
    },
    "sample_52": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 1997 ,",
        "sentence": "At the FIL World Luge Championships , Prock won 13 medals , including five gold ( Men 's singles : 1987 , 1996 ; Mixed team : 1996 , 1997"
    },
    "sample_53": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 1999 )",
        "sentence": "At the FIL World Luge Championships , Prock won 13 medals , including five gold ( Men 's singles : 1987 , 1996 ; Mixed team : 1996 , 1997"
    },
    "sample_54": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": 1990 ,",
        "sentence": "At the FIL World Luge Championships , Prock won 13 medals , including five gold ( Men 's singles : 1987 , 1996 ; Mixed team : 1996 , 1997"
    },
    "sample_55": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": 1991 ,",
        "sentence": "At the FIL World Luge Championships , Prock won 13 medals , including five gold ( Men 's singles : 1987 , 1996 ; Mixed team : 1996 , 1997"
    },
    "sample_56": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 1993 )",
        "sentence": "At the FIL World Luge Championships , Prock won 13 medals , including five gold ( Men 's singles : 1987 , 1996 ; Mixed team : 1996 , 1997"
    },
    "sample_57": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": ": 1995 ,",
        "sentence": "At the FIL World Luge Championships , Prock won 13 medals , including five gold ( Men 's singles : 1987 , 1996 ; Mixed team : 1996 , 1997"
    },
    "sample_58": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": ", 2001 ;",
        "sentence": "At the FIL World Luge Championships , Prock won 13 medals , including five gold ( Men 's singles : 1987 , 1996 ; Mixed team : 1996 , 1997"
    },
    "sample_59": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": ", 2001 )",
        "sentence": "At the FIL World Luge Championships , Prock won 13 medals , including five gold ( Men 's singles : 1987 , 1996 ; Mixed team : 1996 , 1997"
    },
    "sample_60": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the FIL European Luge Championships with",
        "sentence": "Prock won six medals at the FIL European Luge Championships with five in men 's singles ( gold : 1994 , 1998 , 2002 ; silver : 1988 , 1990"
    },
    "sample_61": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": 1994 ,",
        "sentence": "Prock won six medals at the FIL European Luge Championships with five in men 's singles ( gold : 1994 , 1998 , 2002 ; silver : 1988 , 1990"
    },
    "sample_62": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 1998 ,",
        "sentence": "Prock won six medals at the FIL European Luge Championships with five in men 's singles ( gold : 1994 , 1998 , 2002 ; silver : 1988 , 1990"
    },
    "sample_63": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 2002 ;",
        "sentence": "Prock won six medals at the FIL European Luge Championships with five in men 's singles ( gold : 1994 , 1998 , 2002 ; silver : 1988 , 1990"
    },
    "sample_64": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": 1988 ,",
        "sentence": "Prock won six medals at the FIL European Luge Championships with five in men 's singles ( gold : 1994 , 1998 , 2002 ; silver : 1988 , 1990"
    },
    "sample_65": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 1990 )",
        "sentence": "Prock won six medals at the FIL European Luge Championships with five in men 's singles ( gold : 1994 , 1998 , 2002 ; silver : 1988 , 1990"
    },
    "sample_66": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Gregor Schlierenzauer ,",
        "sentence": "He also manages his nephew , Gregor Schlierenzauer , who was second in the 2006-07 entering the FIS Nordic World Ski Championships 2007 in Sapporo , Japan"
    },
    "sample_67": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the FIS Nordic World Ski Championships 2007 in",
        "sentence": "He also manages his nephew , Gregor Schlierenzauer , who was second in the 2006-07 entering the FIS Nordic World Ski Championships 2007 in Sapporo , Japan"
    },
    "sample_68": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Sapporo ,",
        "sentence": "He also manages his nephew , Gregor Schlierenzauer , who was second in the 2006-07 entering the FIS Nordic World Ski Championships 2007 in Sapporo , Japan"
    },
    "sample_69": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Japan <UNK>",
        "sentence": "He also manages his nephew , Gregor Schlierenzauer , who was second in the 2006-07 entering the FIS Nordic World Ski Championships 2007 in Sapporo , Japan"
    },
    "sample_70": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "both Great Britain and",
        "sentence": "He represented both Great Britain and Ireland as a water polo player at the 1920 and 1924 Summer Olympics respectively ."
    },
    "sample_71": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Ireland as",
        "sentence": "He represented both Great Britain and Ireland as a water polo player at the 1920 and 1924 Summer Olympics respectively ."
    },
    "sample_72": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "a water polo player",
        "sentence": "He represented both Great Britain and Ireland as a water polo player at the 1920 and 1924 Summer Olympics respectively ."
    },
    "sample_73": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the 1920 and",
        "sentence": "He represented both Great Britain and Ireland as a water polo player at the 1920 and 1924 Summer Olympics respectively ."
    },
    "sample_74": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and 1924 Summer",
        "sentence": "He represented both Great Britain and Ireland as a water polo player at the 1920 and 1924 Summer Olympics respectively ."
    },
    "sample_75": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "played rugby union for",
        "sentence": "He also played rugby union for Belvedere College , Clongowes Wood College and Ireland ."
    },
    "sample_76": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "for Belvedere College ,",
        "sentence": "He also played rugby union for Belvedere College , Clongowes Wood College and Ireland ."
    },
    "sample_77": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Clongowes Wood College and",
        "sentence": "He also played rugby union for Belvedere College , Clongowes Wood College and Ireland ."
    },
    "sample_78": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Ireland .",
        "sentence": "He also played rugby union for Belvedere College , Clongowes Wood College and Ireland ."
    },
    "sample_79": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the 1920 Summer Olympics Purcell",
        "sentence": "At the 1920 Summer Olympics Purcell , together with Charles Sydney Smith , , Charles Bugbee , , and William Henry Dean , was a member of the Great Britain"
    },
    "sample_80": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "with Charles Sydney Smith ,",
        "sentence": "At the 1920 Summer Olympics Purcell , together with Charles Sydney Smith , , Charles Bugbee , , and William Henry Dean , was a member of the Great Britain"
    },
    "sample_81": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Charles Bugbee ,",
        "sentence": "At the 1920 Summer Olympics Purcell , together with Charles Sydney Smith , , Charles Bugbee , , and William Henry Dean , was a member of the Great Britain"
    },
    "sample_82": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and William Henry Dean ,",
        "sentence": "At the 1920 Summer Olympics Purcell , together with Charles Sydney Smith , , Charles Bugbee , , and William Henry Dean , was a member of the Great Britain"
    },
    "sample_83": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in 1924 he",
        "sentence": "Then in 1924 he captained Ireland ."
    },
    "sample_84": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "captained Ireland .",
        "sentence": "Then in 1924 he captained Ireland ."
    },
    "sample_85": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the 1921 Five Nations Championship ,",
        "sentence": "In the 1921 Five Nations Championship , Purcell played in all four games for Ireland ."
    },
    "sample_86": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "for Ireland .",
        "sentence": "In the 1921 Five Nations Championship , Purcell played in all four games for Ireland ."
    },
    "sample_87": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "against England on",
        "sentence": "He made his debut against England on 12 February ."
    },
    "sample_88": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "against Scotland on",
        "sentence": "He then played against Scotland on 26 February and Wales on 12 March ."
    },
    "sample_89": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Wales on",
        "sentence": "He then played against Scotland on 26 February and Wales on 12 March ."
    },
    "sample_90": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "against France <UNK>",
        "sentence": "He made his final appearance for Ireland against France"
    },
    "sample_91": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "a state highway in",
        "sentence": "State Route 13 ( <UNK> ) is a state highway in the western part of the U.S. state of Alabama ."
    },
    "sample_92": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the U.S. state of",
        "sentence": "State Route 13 ( <UNK> ) is a state highway in the western part of the U.S. state of Alabama ."
    },
    "sample_93": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of Alabama .",
        "sentence": "State Route 13 ( <UNK> ) is a state highway in the western part of the U.S. state of Alabama ."
    },
    "sample_94": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Tennessee state",
        "sentence": "The northern terminus of the route is on <UNK> at the Tennessee state line north of Killen in Lauderdale County ."
    },
    "sample_95": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of Killen in",
        "sentence": "The northern terminus of the route is on <UNK> at the Tennessee state line north of Killen in Lauderdale County ."
    },
    "sample_96": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Lauderdale County .",
        "sentence": "The northern terminus of the route is on <UNK> at the Tennessee state line north of Killen in Lauderdale County ."
    },
    "sample_97": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "southern Fayette County ,",
        "sentence": "As a signed route , the southern terminus of the route is at the junction of <UNK> and in southern Fayette County , and the northern terminus as at <UNK>"
    },
    "sample_98": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of Russellville in",
        "sentence": "As a signed route , the southern terminus of the route is at the junction of <UNK> and in southern Fayette County , and the northern terminus as at <UNK>"
    },
    "sample_99": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Franklin County .",
        "sentence": "As a signed route , the southern terminus of the route is at the junction of <UNK> and in southern Fayette County , and the northern terminus as at <UNK>"
    },
    "sample_100": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Walker ,",
        "sentence": "<UNK> leads through rural areas of Fayette , Walker , Winston , Marion and Franklin"
    },
    "sample_101": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Winston ,",
        "sentence": "<UNK> leads through rural areas of Fayette , Walker , Winston , Marion and Franklin"
    },
    "sample_102": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Marion and",
        "sentence": "<UNK> leads through rural areas of Fayette , Walker , Winston , Marion and Franklin"
    },
    "sample_103": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Franklin <UNK>",
        "sentence": "<UNK> leads through rural areas of Fayette , Walker , Winston , Marion and Franklin"
    },
    "sample_104": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "of Greek or",
        "sentence": "Christine is a feminine name of Greek or origin ."
    },
    "sample_105": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "\" Messiah \"",
        "sentence": "It is derived from the word Christ , which is the Greek translation of the Hebrew word \" Messiah \" ."
    },
    "sample_106": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "a French variant",
        "sentence": "As a French variant of the Greek name Christina , it is a name in regular usage in French , English , German , Scandinavia n , Dutch and cultures"
    },
    "sample_107": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the Greek name",
        "sentence": "As a French variant of the Greek name Christina , it is a name in regular usage in French , English , German , Scandinavia n , Dutch and cultures"
    },
    "sample_108": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "name Christina ,",
        "sentence": "As a French variant of the Greek name Christina , it is a name in regular usage in French , English , German , Scandinavia n , Dutch and cultures"
    },
    "sample_109": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "in French ,",
        "sentence": "As a French variant of the Greek name Christina , it is a name in regular usage in French , English , German , Scandinavia n , Dutch and cultures"
    },
    "sample_110": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": ", English ,",
        "sentence": "As a French variant of the Greek name Christina , it is a name in regular usage in French , English , German , Scandinavia n , Dutch and cultures"
    },
    "sample_111": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": ", German ,",
        "sentence": "As a French variant of the Greek name Christina , it is a name in regular usage in French , English , German , Scandinavia n , Dutch and cultures"
    },
    "sample_112": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Scandinavia n",
        "sentence": "As a French variant of the Greek name Christina , it is a name in regular usage in French , English , German , Scandinavia n , Dutch and cultures"
    },
    "sample_113": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": ", Dutch and",
        "sentence": "As a French variant of the Greek name Christina , it is a name in regular usage in French , English , German , Scandinavia n , Dutch and cultures"
    },
    "sample_114": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "are Christina ,",
        "sentence": "Other ways to say Christine are Christina , , , , Kirsten , , ( most used in Spain and Latin American countries ) , etc. ."
    },
    "sample_115": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Kirsten ,",
        "sentence": "Other ways to say Christine are Christina , , , , Kirsten , , ( most used in Spain and Latin American countries ) , etc. ."
    },
    "sample_116": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Spain and",
        "sentence": "Other ways to say Christine are Christina , , , , Kirsten , , ( most used in Spain and Latin American countries ) , etc. ."
    },
    "sample_117": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "and Latin American countries",
        "sentence": "Other ways to say Christine are Christina , , , , Kirsten , , ( most used in Spain and Latin American countries ) , etc. ."
    },
    "sample_118": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the United States <UNK>",
        "sentence": "It is a popular name ; for example , in 1968 , it was the 14th most <UNK> name for girls in the United States"
    },
    "sample_119": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the period 4",
        "sentence": "d-block contraction ( sometimes called <UNK> contraction ) is a term used in chemistry to describe the effect of having full d orbitals on the period 4 elements ."
    },
    "sample_120": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Ga ,",
        "sentence": "The elements in question are the Ga , Ge , As , Se and Br ."
    },
    "sample_121": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Ge ,",
        "sentence": "The elements in question are the Ga , Ge , As , Se and Br ."
    },
    "sample_122": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", As ,",
        "sentence": "The elements in question are the Ga , Ge , As , Se and Br ."
    },
    "sample_123": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Se and",
        "sentence": "The elements in question are the Ga , Ge , As , Se and Br ."
    },
    "sample_124": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Br .",
        "sentence": "The elements in question are the Ga , Ge , As , Se and Br ."
    },
    "sample_125": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the group 13 elements to",
        "sentence": "d-block contraction is best illustrated by comparing some properties of the group 13 elements to highlight the effect on gallium ."
    },
    "sample_126": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "elements B ,",
        "sentence": "The second table below shows the trend in the sum of the first three ionization potentials for the elements B , Al , Sc , Y , La ."
    },
    "sample_127": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Al ,",
        "sentence": "The second table below shows the trend in the sum of the first three ionization potentials for the elements B , Al , Sc , Y , La ."
    },
    "sample_128": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Sc ,",
        "sentence": "The second table below shows the trend in the sum of the first three ionization potentials for the elements B , Al , Sc , Y , La ."
    },
    "sample_129": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Y ,",
        "sentence": "The second table below shows the trend in the sum of the first three ionization potentials for the elements B , Al , Sc , Y , La ."
    },
    "sample_130": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", La .",
        "sentence": "The second table below shows the trend in the sum of the first three ionization potentials for the elements B , Al , Sc , Y , La ."
    },
    "sample_131": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Sc ,",
        "sentence": "Sc , Y , La are group 3 element s and have three valence electrons above a noble gas electron core ."
    },
    "sample_132": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Y ,",
        "sentence": "Sc , Y , La are group 3 element s and have three valence electrons above a noble gas electron core ."
    },
    "sample_133": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", La are",
        "sentence": "Sc , Y , La are group 3 element s and have three valence electrons above a noble gas electron core ."
    },
    "sample_134": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "are group 3 element s",
        "sentence": "Sc , Y , La are group 3 element s and have three valence electrons above a noble gas electron core ."
    },
    "sample_135": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "a noble gas electron",
        "sentence": "Sc , Y , La are group 3 element s and have three valence electrons above a noble gas electron core ."
    },
    "sample_136": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the group 13 elements this",
        "sentence": "In contrast to the group 13 elements this sequence shows a smooth reduction ."
    },
    "sample_137": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the inert pair effect become",
        "sentence": "Care must be taken in interpreting the ionization potentials for indium and thallium , other effects e.g. the inert pair effect become increasingly important for the heavier members of the"
    },
    "sample_138": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the lanthanide contraction <UNK>",
        "sentence": "The d-block contraction can be compared to the lanthanide contraction"
    },
    "sample_139": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Duke University Library",
        "sentence": "The Kenneth Willis Clark Collection of Greek Manuscripts in Duke University Library contains ninety-eight manuscript s -- in both roll and codex form -- dating from the 9th to the"
    },
    "sample_140": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "ninety-eight manuscript s",
        "sentence": "The Kenneth Willis Clark Collection of Greek Manuscripts in Duke University Library contains ninety-eight manuscript s -- in both roll and codex form -- dating from the 9th to the"
    },
    "sample_141": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Duke Divinity School bought",
        "sentence": "Professor H. Branscomb of the Duke Divinity School bought a manuscript of the Greek New Testament in the Munich bookshop ."
    },
    "sample_142": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "Greek New Testament in",
        "sentence": "Professor H. Branscomb of the Duke Divinity School bought a manuscript of the Greek New Testament in the Munich bookshop ."
    },
    "sample_143": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Munich bookshop",
        "sentence": "Professor H. Branscomb of the Duke Divinity School bought a manuscript of the Greek New Testament in the Munich bookshop ."
    },
    "sample_144": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the New Testament .",
        "sentence": "In the collection are 27 manuscripts which contain texts of the New Testament ."
    },
    "sample_145": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> 4 ,",
        "sentence": "4 , 5 , 6 , 15 , 22 , 25 , 31 , 38 , , and 64 ."
    },
    "sample_146": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 5 ,",
        "sentence": "4 , 5 , 6 , 15 , 22 , 25 , 31 , 38 , , and 64 ."
    },
    "sample_147": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 6 ,",
        "sentence": "4 , 5 , 6 , 15 , 22 , 25 , 31 , 38 , , and 64 ."
    },
    "sample_148": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 15 ,",
        "sentence": "4 , 5 , 6 , 15 , 22 , 25 , 31 , 38 , , and 64 ."
    },
    "sample_149": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 22 ,",
        "sentence": "4 , 5 , 6 , 15 , 22 , 25 , 31 , 38 , , and 64 ."
    },
    "sample_150": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 25 ,",
        "sentence": "4 , 5 , 6 , 15 , 22 , 25 , 31 , 38 , , and 64 ."
    },
    "sample_151": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 31 ,",
        "sentence": "4 , 5 , 6 , 15 , 22 , 25 , 31 , 38 , , and 64 ."
    },
    "sample_152": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 38 ,",
        "sentence": "4 , 5 , 6 , 15 , 22 , 25 , 31 , 38 , , and 64 ."
    },
    "sample_153": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and 64 .",
        "sentence": "4 , 5 , 6 , 15 , 22 , 25 , 31 , 38 , , and 64 ."
    },
    "sample_154": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "as Codex <UNK> ,",
        "sentence": "Ms. 60 , also known as Codex <UNK> , is most notable among this group ."
    },
    "sample_155": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "some Lectionaries in",
        "sentence": "There are also some Lectionaries in collection , represented by MSS ."
    },
    "sample_156": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> 1 ,",
        "sentence": "1 , 2 , 10 , 12 , 20 , 24 , 27 , 28 , 39 , 43 , 65 , 82 , 83 , 85 ."
    },
    "sample_157": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 2 ,",
        "sentence": "1 , 2 , 10 , 12 , 20 , 24 , 27 , 28 , 39 , 43 , 65 , 82 , 83 , 85 ."
    },
    "sample_158": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 10 ,",
        "sentence": "1 , 2 , 10 , 12 , 20 , 24 , 27 , 28 , 39 , 43 , 65 , 82 , 83 , 85 ."
    },
    "sample_159": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 12 ,",
        "sentence": "1 , 2 , 10 , 12 , 20 , 24 , 27 , 28 , 39 , 43 , 65 , 82 , 83 , 85 ."
    },
    "sample_160": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 24 ,",
        "sentence": "1 , 2 , 10 , 12 , 20 , 24 , 27 , 28 , 39 , 43 , 65 , 82 , 83 , 85 ."
    },
    "sample_161": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 27 ,",
        "sentence": "1 , 2 , 10 , 12 , 20 , 24 , 27 , 28 , 39 , 43 , 65 , 82 , 83 , 85 ."
    },
    "sample_162": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 28 ,",
        "sentence": "1 , 2 , 10 , 12 , 20 , 24 , 27 , 28 , 39 , 43 , 65 , 82 , 83 , 85 ."
    },
    "sample_163": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 39 ,",
        "sentence": "1 , 2 , 10 , 12 , 20 , 24 , 27 , 28 , 39 , 43 , 65 , 82 , 83 , 85 ."
    },
    "sample_164": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 43 ,",
        "sentence": "1 , 2 , 10 , 12 , 20 , 24 , 27 , 28 , 39 , 43 , 65 , 82 , 83 , 85 ."
    },
    "sample_165": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 65 ,",
        "sentence": "1 , 2 , 10 , 12 , 20 , 24 , 27 , 28 , 39 , 43 , 65 , 82 , 83 , 85 ."
    },
    "sample_166": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 82 ,",
        "sentence": "1 , 2 , 10 , 12 , 20 , 24 , 27 , 28 , 39 , 43 , 65 , 82 , 83 , 85 ."
    },
    "sample_167": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", 83 ,",
        "sentence": "1 , 2 , 10 , 12 , 20 , 24 , 27 , 28 , 39 , 43 , 65 , 82 , 83 , 85 ."
    },
    "sample_168": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Ms 65 (",
        "sentence": "Ms 65 ( ℓ 1839 ) was written in 11th century ."
    },
    "sample_169": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "6th UEM European",
        "sentence": "The 2009 European Pairs Speedway Championship will be the 6th UEM European Pairs Speedway Championship season ."
    },
    "sample_170": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "UEM European Pairs Speedway Championship season",
        "sentence": "The 2009 European Pairs Speedway Championship will be the 6th UEM European Pairs Speedway Championship season ."
    },
    "sample_171": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "September 2009 in",
        "sentence": "The Final was held on 26 September 2009 in Miskolc , Hungary ; it was second Final in Hungary , but first in Miskolc ."
    },
    "sample_172": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Miskolc ,",
        "sentence": "The Final was held on 26 September 2009 in Miskolc , Hungary ; it was second Final in Hungary , but first in Miskolc ."
    },
    "sample_173": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Hungary ;",
        "sentence": "The Final was held on 26 September 2009 in Miskolc , Hungary ; it was second Final in Hungary , but first in Miskolc ."
    },
    "sample_174": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "by Czech Republic pair and",
        "sentence": "The championship was won by Czech Republic pair and they beat Russia and the defending Champions Poland ."
    },
    "sample_175": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "beat Russia and",
        "sentence": "The championship was won by Czech Republic pair and they beat Russia and the defending Champions Poland ."
    },
    "sample_176": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "Champions Poland .",
        "sentence": "The championship was won by Czech Republic pair and they beat Russia and the defending Champions Poland ."
    },
    "sample_177": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "Champion Poland ,",
        "sentence": "In the Final will be the defending Champion Poland , Czech Republic ( 2nd place in 2008 Final ) , Russia ( 3rd place ) , host team Hungary ("
    },
    "sample_178": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Czech Republic (",
        "sentence": "In the Final will be the defending Champion Poland , Czech Republic ( 2nd place in 2008 Final ) , Russia ( 3rd place ) , host team Hungary ("
    },
    "sample_179": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Russia (",
        "sentence": "In the Final will be the defending Champion Poland , Czech Republic ( 2nd place in 2008 Final ) , Russia ( 3rd place ) , host team Hungary ("
    },
    "sample_180": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "team Hungary (",
        "sentence": "In the Final will be the defending Champion Poland , Czech Republic ( 2nd place in 2008 Final ) , Russia ( 3rd place ) , host team Hungary ("
    },
    "sample_181": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Latvia (",
        "sentence": "In the Final will be the defending Champion Poland , Czech Republic ( 2nd place in 2008 Final ) , Russia ( 3rd place ) , host team Hungary ("
    },
    "sample_182": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "In Ljubljana ,",
        "sentence": "In Ljubljana , Slovenia on May 13 will be Austria ( 6th place ) , Germany ( 7th place ) , Ukraine , Finland , host team Slovenia , Italy"
    },
    "sample_183": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Slovenia on",
        "sentence": "In Ljubljana , Slovenia on May 13 will be Austria ( 6th place ) , Germany ( 7th place ) , Ukraine , Finland , host team Slovenia , Italy"
    },
    "sample_184": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "be Austria (",
        "sentence": "In Ljubljana , Slovenia on May 13 will be Austria ( 6th place ) , Germany ( 7th place ) , Ukraine , Finland , host team Slovenia , Italy"
    },
    "sample_185": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Germany (",
        "sentence": "In Ljubljana , Slovenia on May 13 will be Austria ( 6th place ) , Germany ( 7th place ) , Ukraine , Finland , host team Slovenia , Italy"
    },
    "sample_186": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Ukraine ,",
        "sentence": "In Ljubljana , Slovenia on May 13 will be Austria ( 6th place ) , Germany ( 7th place ) , Ukraine , Finland , host team Slovenia , Italy"
    },
    "sample_187": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Finland ,",
        "sentence": "In Ljubljana , Slovenia on May 13 will be Austria ( 6th place ) , Germany ( 7th place ) , Ukraine , Finland , host team Slovenia , Italy"
    },
    "sample_188": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "team Slovenia ,",
        "sentence": "In Ljubljana , Slovenia on May 13 will be Austria ( 6th place ) , Germany ( 7th place ) , Ukraine , Finland , host team Slovenia , Italy"
    },
    "sample_189": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Italy and",
        "sentence": "In Ljubljana , Slovenia on May 13 will be Austria ( 6th place ) , Germany ( 7th place ) , Ukraine , Finland , host team Slovenia , Italy"
    },
    "sample_190": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Croatia <UNK>",
        "sentence": "In Ljubljana , Slovenia on May 13 will be Austria ( 6th place ) , Germany ( 7th place ) , Ukraine , Finland , host team Slovenia , Italy"
    },
    "sample_191": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "when Iowa sent",
        "sentence": "Iowa 's 10th congressional district existed from 1883 to 1933 , when Iowa sent eleven congressmen to the United States House of Representatives ."
    },
    "sample_192": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the United States House of Representatives .",
        "sentence": "Iowa 's 10th congressional district existed from 1883 to 1933 , when Iowa sent eleven congressmen to the United States House of Representatives ."
    },
    "sample_193": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of Worth ,",
        "sentence": "From 1883 to 1886 , the district included the north-central Iowa counties of Worth , Cerro Gordo , Franklin , Hardin , Story , Wright , Hamilton , Humboldt ,"
    },
    "sample_194": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Cerro Gordo ,",
        "sentence": "From 1883 to 1886 , the district included the north-central Iowa counties of Worth , Cerro Gordo , Franklin , Hardin , Story , Wright , Hamilton , Humboldt ,"
    },
    "sample_195": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Franklin ,",
        "sentence": "From 1883 to 1886 , the district included the north-central Iowa counties of Worth , Cerro Gordo , Franklin , Hardin , Story , Wright , Hamilton , Humboldt ,"
    },
    "sample_196": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Hardin ,",
        "sentence": "From 1883 to 1886 , the district included the north-central Iowa counties of Worth , Cerro Gordo , Franklin , Hardin , Story , Wright , Hamilton , Humboldt ,"
    },
    "sample_197": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Story ,",
        "sentence": "From 1883 to 1886 , the district included the north-central Iowa counties of Worth , Cerro Gordo , Franklin , Hardin , Story , Wright , Hamilton , Humboldt ,"
    },
    "sample_198": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Wright ,",
        "sentence": "From 1883 to 1886 , the district included the north-central Iowa counties of Worth , Cerro Gordo , Franklin , Hardin , Story , Wright , Hamilton , Humboldt ,"
    },
    "sample_199": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Hamilton ,",
        "sentence": "From 1883 to 1886 , the district included the north-central Iowa counties of Worth , Cerro Gordo , Franklin , Hardin , Story , Wright , Hamilton , Humboldt ,"
    },
    "sample_200": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Humboldt ,",
        "sentence": "From 1883 to 1886 , the district included the north-central Iowa counties of Worth , Cerro Gordo , Franklin , Hardin , Story , Wright , Hamilton , Humboldt ,"
    },
    "sample_201": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Hancock ,",
        "sentence": "From 1883 to 1886 , the district included the north-central Iowa counties of Worth , Cerro Gordo , Franklin , Hardin , Story , Wright , Hamilton , Humboldt ,"
    },
    "sample_202": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Kossuth ,",
        "sentence": "From 1883 to 1886 , the district included the north-central Iowa counties of Worth , Cerro Gordo , Franklin , Hardin , Story , Wright , Hamilton , Humboldt ,"
    },
    "sample_203": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Winnebago ,",
        "sentence": "From 1883 to 1886 , the district included the north-central Iowa counties of Worth , Cerro Gordo , Franklin , Hardin , Story , Wright , Hamilton , Humboldt ,"
    },
    "sample_204": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Webster ,",
        "sentence": "From 1883 to 1886 , the district included the north-central Iowa counties of Worth , Cerro Gordo , Franklin , Hardin , Story , Wright , Hamilton , Humboldt ,"
    },
    "sample_205": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Boone .",
        "sentence": "From 1883 to 1886 , the district included the north-central Iowa counties of Worth , Cerro Gordo , Franklin , Hardin , Story , Wright , Hamilton , Humboldt ,"
    },
    "sample_206": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Calhoun ,",
        "sentence": "From 1886 until 1933 , the district was made up of Boone , Calhoun , Carroll , Crawford , Emmet , Greene , Hamilton , Humboldt , Kossuth , Palo"
    },
    "sample_207": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Carroll ,",
        "sentence": "From 1886 until 1933 , the district was made up of Boone , Calhoun , Carroll , Crawford , Emmet , Greene , Hamilton , Humboldt , Kossuth , Palo"
    },
    "sample_208": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Crawford ,",
        "sentence": "From 1886 until 1933 , the district was made up of Boone , Calhoun , Carroll , Crawford , Emmet , Greene , Hamilton , Humboldt , Kossuth , Palo"
    },
    "sample_209": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Emmet ,",
        "sentence": "From 1886 until 1933 , the district was made up of Boone , Calhoun , Carroll , Crawford , Emmet , Greene , Hamilton , Humboldt , Kossuth , Palo"
    },
    "sample_210": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Greene ,",
        "sentence": "From 1886 until 1933 , the district was made up of Boone , Calhoun , Carroll , Crawford , Emmet , Greene , Hamilton , Humboldt , Kossuth , Palo"
    },
    "sample_211": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Palo Alto ,",
        "sentence": "From 1886 until 1933 , the district was made up of Boone , Calhoun , Carroll , Crawford , Emmet , Greene , Hamilton , Humboldt , Kossuth , Palo"
    },
    "sample_212": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Pocahontas ,",
        "sentence": "From 1886 until 1933 , the district was made up of Boone , Calhoun , Carroll , Crawford , Emmet , Greene , Hamilton , Humboldt , Kossuth , Palo"
    },
    "sample_213": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Iowa General Assembly refused",
        "sentence": "After 1886 , the boundaries of the district never changed ; the Iowa General Assembly refused to reapportion its districts until the loss of two seats following the 1930 census"
    },
    "sample_214": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "-- Fort Dodge --",
        "sentence": "During that period , it included only one of Iowa 's twenty largest cities -- Fort Dodge -- and included counties that had been relatively slow to settle ."
    },
    "sample_215": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "and 11th Districts",
        "sentence": "By 1890 , the continued disproportionate increase in the population of the 10th and 11th Districts caused some to predict that the General Assembly would need to reduce the area"
    },
    "sample_216": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Republican Party .",
        "sentence": "Every congressman elected from this district was a member of the Republican Party ."
    },
    "sample_217": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "( Jonathan P. Dolliver and",
        "sentence": "Two 10th district congressmen ( Jonathan P. Dolliver and ) became well-known members of the U.S. Senate and sought national office ."
    },
    "sample_218": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Fred C. Gilchrist ,",
        "sentence": "The last congressman elected by the old 10th district , Fred C. Gilchrist , was elected in the new 8th district in 1932 ."
    },
    "sample_219": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "( Merwin Coad <UNK>",
        "sentence": "It was only after that district elected a Democrat ( Merwin Coad"
    },
    "sample_220": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Rochdale --",
        "sentence": "Derrick Schofield ( born 1928 in Rochdale -- died 25 August 1999 ( aged 71 ) ) was an English professional rugby league footballer of the 1940s and '50s ,"
    },
    "sample_221": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "an English professional",
        "sentence": "Derrick Schofield ( born 1928 in Rochdale -- died 25 August 1999 ( aged 71 ) ) was an English professional rugby league footballer of the 1940s and '50s ,"
    },
    "sample_222": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "professional rugby league footballer",
        "sentence": "Derrick Schofield ( born 1928 in Rochdale -- died 25 August 1999 ( aged 71 ) ) was an English professional rugby league footballer of the 1940s and '50s ,"
    },
    "sample_223": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "for Great Britain ,",
        "sentence": "Derrick Schofield ( born 1928 in Rochdale -- died 25 August 1999 ( aged 71 ) ) was an English professional rugby league footballer of the 1940s and '50s ,"
    },
    "sample_224": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", England ,",
        "sentence": "Derrick Schofield ( born 1928 in Rochdale -- died 25 August 1999 ( aged 71 ) ) was an English professional rugby league footballer of the 1940s and '50s ,"
    },
    "sample_225": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Lancashire ,",
        "sentence": "Derrick Schofield ( born 1928 in Rochdale -- died 25 August 1999 ( aged 71 ) ) was an English professional rugby league footballer of the 1940s and '50s ,"
    },
    "sample_226": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "for Rochdale Hornets (",
        "sentence": "Derrick Schofield ( born 1928 in Rochdale -- died 25 August 1999 ( aged 71 ) ) was an English professional rugby league footballer of the 1940s and '50s ,"
    },
    "sample_227": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Halifax ,",
        "sentence": "Derrick Schofield ( born 1928 in Rochdale -- died 25 August 1999 ( aged 71 ) ) was an English professional rugby league footballer of the 1940s and '50s ,"
    },
    "sample_228": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Castleford and",
        "sentence": "Derrick Schofield ( born 1928 in Rochdale -- died 25 August 1999 ( aged 71 ) ) was an English professional rugby league footballer of the 1940s and '50s ,"
    },
    "sample_229": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Dewsbury ,",
        "sentence": "Derrick Schofield ( born 1928 in Rochdale -- died 25 August 1999 ( aged 71 ) ) was an English professional rugby league footballer of the 1940s and '50s ,"
    },
    "sample_230": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "for England while",
        "sentence": "Derrick Schofield won caps for England while at Rochdale in 1952 against Wales , in 1953 against France , and won a cap for Great Britain while at Halifax in"
    },
    "sample_231": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "for Great Britain while",
        "sentence": "Derrick Schofield won caps for England while at Rochdale in 1952 against Wales , in 1953 against France , and won a cap for Great Britain while at Halifax in"
    },
    "sample_232": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "represented Great Britain while",
        "sentence": "Derrick Schofield also represented Great Britain while at Halifax between 1952 and 1956 against France ( 1 non - Test match ) ."
    },
    "sample_233": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "- Test match",
        "sentence": "Derrick Schofield also represented Great Britain while at Halifax between 1952 and 1956 against France ( 1 non - Test match ) ."
    },
    "sample_234": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Halifax 's",
        "sentence": "Derrick Schofield played Right - , i.e. number 12 , in Halifax 's 4-4 draw with Warrington in the Challenge Cup final at Wembley Stadium on Saturday 1 May 1954"
    },
    "sample_235": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "with Warrington in",
        "sentence": "Derrick Schofield played Right - , i.e. number 12 , in Halifax 's 4-4 draw with Warrington in the Challenge Cup final at Wembley Stadium on Saturday 1 May 1954"
    },
    "sample_236": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the Challenge Cup final",
        "sentence": "Derrick Schofield played Right - , i.e. number 12 , in Halifax 's 4-4 draw with Warrington in the Challenge Cup final at Wembley Stadium on Saturday 1 May 1954"
    },
    "sample_237": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "at Wembley Stadium on",
        "sentence": "Derrick Schofield played Right - , i.e. number 12 , in Halifax 's 4-4 draw with Warrington in the Challenge Cup final at Wembley Stadium on Saturday 1 May 1954"
    },
    "sample_238": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Challenge Cup final",
        "sentence": "Derrick Schofield played Right - , i.e. number 12 , in Halifax 's 4-4 draw with Warrington in the Challenge Cup final at Wembley Stadium on Saturday 1 May 1954"
    },
    "sample_239": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "at Odsal Stadium ,",
        "sentence": "Derrick Schofield played Right - , i.e. number 12 , in Halifax 's 4-4 draw with Warrington in the Challenge Cup final at Wembley Stadium on Saturday 1 May 1954"
    },
    "sample_240": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Bradford <UNK>",
        "sentence": "Derrick Schofield played Right - , i.e. number 12 , in Halifax 's 4-4 draw with Warrington in the Challenge Cup final at Wembley Stadium on Saturday 1 May 1954"
    },
    "sample_241": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": Chester County ,",
        "sentence": "<UNK> serves the following counties in Tennessee : Chester County , Decatur County , Hardeman County , Hardin County , Haywood County , Henderson County , Madison County and McNairy"
    },
    "sample_242": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Decatur County ,",
        "sentence": "<UNK> serves the following counties in Tennessee : Chester County , Decatur County , Hardeman County , Hardin County , Haywood County , Henderson County , Madison County and McNairy"
    },
    "sample_243": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Hardeman County ,",
        "sentence": "<UNK> serves the following counties in Tennessee : Chester County , Decatur County , Hardeman County , Hardin County , Haywood County , Henderson County , Madison County and McNairy"
    },
    "sample_244": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Hardin County ,",
        "sentence": "<UNK> serves the following counties in Tennessee : Chester County , Decatur County , Hardeman County , Hardin County , Haywood County , Henderson County , Madison County and McNairy"
    },
    "sample_245": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Haywood County ,",
        "sentence": "<UNK> serves the following counties in Tennessee : Chester County , Decatur County , Hardeman County , Hardin County , Haywood County , Henderson County , Madison County and McNairy"
    },
    "sample_246": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Henderson County ,",
        "sentence": "<UNK> serves the following counties in Tennessee : Chester County , Decatur County , Hardeman County , Hardin County , Haywood County , Henderson County , Madison County and McNairy"
    },
    "sample_247": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Madison County and",
        "sentence": "<UNK> serves the following counties in Tennessee : Chester County , Decatur County , Hardeman County , Hardin County , Haywood County , Henderson County , Madison County and McNairy"
    },
    "sample_248": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and McNairy County .",
        "sentence": "<UNK> serves the following counties in Tennessee : Chester County , Decatur County , Hardeman County , Hardin County , Haywood County , Henderson County , Madison County and McNairy"
    },
    "sample_249": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Chester County ,",
        "sentence": "Chester County , Crockett County , Decatur County , , Gibson County , Hardeman County , Hardin County , Haywood County , Henderson County , Lauderdale County , McNairy County"
    },
    "sample_250": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Crockett County ,",
        "sentence": "Chester County , Crockett County , Decatur County , , Gibson County , Hardeman County , Hardin County , Haywood County , Henderson County , Lauderdale County , McNairy County"
    },
    "sample_251": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Decatur County ,",
        "sentence": "Chester County , Crockett County , Decatur County , , Gibson County , Hardeman County , Hardin County , Haywood County , Henderson County , Lauderdale County , McNairy County"
    },
    "sample_252": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Gibson County ,",
        "sentence": "Chester County , Crockett County , Decatur County , , Gibson County , Hardeman County , Hardin County , Haywood County , Henderson County , Lauderdale County , McNairy County"
    },
    "sample_253": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Hardeman County ,",
        "sentence": "Chester County , Crockett County , Decatur County , , Gibson County , Hardeman County , Hardin County , Haywood County , Henderson County , Lauderdale County , McNairy County"
    },
    "sample_254": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Hardin County ,",
        "sentence": "Chester County , Crockett County , Decatur County , , Gibson County , Hardeman County , Hardin County , Haywood County , Henderson County , Lauderdale County , McNairy County"
    },
    "sample_255": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Haywood County ,",
        "sentence": "Chester County , Crockett County , Decatur County , , Gibson County , Hardeman County , Hardin County , Haywood County , Henderson County , Lauderdale County , McNairy County"
    },
    "sample_256": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Henderson County ,",
        "sentence": "Chester County , Crockett County , Decatur County , , Gibson County , Hardeman County , Hardin County , Haywood County , Henderson County , Lauderdale County , McNairy County"
    },
    "sample_257": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Lauderdale County ,",
        "sentence": "Chester County , Crockett County , Decatur County , , Gibson County , Hardeman County , Hardin County , Haywood County , Henderson County , Lauderdale County , McNairy County"
    },
    "sample_258": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", McNairy County ,",
        "sentence": "Chester County , Crockett County , Decatur County , , Gibson County , Hardeman County , Hardin County , Haywood County , Henderson County , Lauderdale County , McNairy County"
    },
    "sample_259": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Tipton County .",
        "sentence": "Chester County , Crockett County , Decatur County , , Gibson County , Hardeman County , Hardin County , Haywood County , Henderson County , Lauderdale County , McNairy County"
    },
    "sample_260": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Jackson , Tennessee <UNK>",
        "sentence": "The <UNK> office is located in Jackson , Tennessee"
    },
    "sample_261": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "a World Cup alpine",
        "sentence": "Marcel Hirscher ( born March 2 , 1989 ) is a World Cup alpine ski racer from Austria ."
    },
    "sample_262": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "Cup alpine ski racer from",
        "sentence": "Marcel Hirscher ( born March 2 , 1989 ) is a World Cup alpine ski racer from Austria ."
    },
    "sample_263": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "from Austria .",
        "sentence": "Marcel Hirscher ( born March 2 , 1989 ) is a World Cup alpine ski racer from Austria ."
    },
    "sample_264": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in <UNK> ,",
        "sentence": "Born in <UNK> , Salzburg , Hirscher made his World Cup debut in March 2007 ."
    },
    "sample_265": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Salzburg ,",
        "sentence": "Born in <UNK> , Salzburg , Hirscher made his World Cup debut in March 2007 ."
    },
    "sample_266": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "March 2007 .",
        "sentence": "Born in <UNK> , Salzburg , Hirscher made his World Cup debut in March 2007 ."
    },
    "sample_267": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the 2010 Winter Olympics ,",
        "sentence": "At the 2010 Winter Olympics , Hirscher placed fourth in the and fifth in the at ."
    },
    "sample_268": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the 2009 World Championships ,",
        "sentence": "He placed fourth in the at the 2009 World Championships , but broke his ankle the weekend preceding the 2011 World Championships , which ended his 2011 season ."
    },
    "sample_269": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the 2011 World Championships ,",
        "sentence": "He placed fourth in the at the 2009 World Championships , but broke his ankle the weekend preceding the 2011 World Championships , which ended his 2011 season ."
    },
    "sample_270": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "his 2011 season",
        "sentence": "He placed fourth in the at the 2009 World Championships , but broke his ankle the weekend preceding the 2011 World Championships , which ended his 2011 season ."
    },
    "sample_271": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in 2012 with",
        "sentence": "Returning after injury , Hirscher had his best season in 2012 with 9 victories and a total of 14 podiums , all in the two technical events ( except for"
    },
    "sample_272": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "in 2013 with",
        "sentence": "Hirscher won the overall World Cup title again in 2013 with 6 victories ; he also won the slalom title and was runner-up in giant slalom ."
    },
    "sample_273": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "over Ted Ligety in",
        "sentence": "The only race in either slalom or giant slalom where he finished outside top 3 was the giant slalom in Adelboden , where after leading after the first run and"
    },
    "sample_274": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "Austrian Stephan Eberharter in",
        "sentence": "He became the first male racer to retain the overall World Cup title since fellow Austrian Stephan Eberharter in 2002 and 2003"
    },
    "sample_275": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in 2002 and",
        "sentence": "He became the first male racer to retain the overall World Cup title since fellow Austrian Stephan Eberharter in 2002 and 2003"
    },
    "sample_276": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "and 2003 <UNK>",
        "sentence": "He became the first male racer to retain the overall World Cup title since fellow Austrian Stephan Eberharter in 2002 and 2003"
    },
    "sample_277": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "represents Harvard University in",
        "sentence": "The Harvard Crimson men 's lacrosse team represents Harvard University in National Collegiate Athletic Association ( NCAA ) Division I men 's lacrosse ."
    },
    "sample_278": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in National Collegiate Athletic Association (",
        "sentence": "The Harvard Crimson men 's lacrosse team represents Harvard University in National Collegiate Athletic Association ( NCAA ) Division I men 's lacrosse ."
    },
    "sample_279": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": ") Division I men",
        "sentence": "The Harvard Crimson men 's lacrosse team represents Harvard University in National Collegiate Athletic Association ( NCAA ) Division I men 's lacrosse ."
    },
    "sample_280": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "'s lacrosse .",
        "sentence": "The Harvard Crimson men 's lacrosse team represents Harvard University in National Collegiate Athletic Association ( NCAA ) Division I men 's lacrosse ."
    },
    "sample_281": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the Ivy League and",
        "sentence": "Harvard competes as a member of the Ivy League and plays its home games at Cumnock Turf and Harvard Stadium in Cambridge , Massachusetts ."
    },
    "sample_282": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Harvard Stadium in",
        "sentence": "Harvard competes as a member of the Ivy League and plays its home games at Cumnock Turf and Harvard Stadium in Cambridge , Massachusetts ."
    },
    "sample_283": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Cambridge , Massachusetts .",
        "sentence": "Harvard competes as a member of the Ivy League and plays its home games at Cumnock Turf and Harvard Stadium in Cambridge , Massachusetts ."
    },
    "sample_284": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "alongside New York University and",
        "sentence": "Harvard fielded its first lacrosse team in 1878 , and the following year , joined the United States National Amateur Lacrosse Association alongside New York University and nine club teams"
    },
    "sample_285": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "defeated Princeton to",
        "sentence": "In 1881 , Harvard defeated Princeton to win the first intercollegiate lacrosse tournament ."
    },
    "sample_286": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "established Yale lacrosse team",
        "sentence": "In 1882 , the Intercollegiate Lacrosse Association was formed , and the following season also inducted the newly established Yale lacrosse team ."
    },
    "sample_287": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and strength of schedule .",
        "sentence": "Championships were awarded in each division based on record and strength of schedule ."
    },
    "sample_288": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "director ordered home its one black player rather",
        "sentence": "In 1941 , Navy refused to play the integrated Harvard team , so its athletic director ordered home its one black player rather than forfeit the game ."
    },
    "sample_289": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "In 1971 ,",
        "sentence": "In 1971 , the NCAA established the national championship tournament ."
    },
    "sample_290": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the national championship tournament .",
        "sentence": "In 1971 , the NCAA established the national championship tournament ."
    },
    "sample_291": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in 1980 ,",
        "sentence": "Harvard made its first appearance in 1980 , when it lost in the first round to Johns Hopkins , 16 -- 12 ."
    },
    "sample_292": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "to Johns Hopkins ,",
        "sentence": "Harvard made its first appearance in 1980 , when it lost in the first round to Johns Hopkins , 16 -- 12 ."
    },
    "sample_293": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in 1988 and",
        "sentence": "The Crimson returned to the event in 1988 and were edge , 10 -- 9 , by Navy in the opening round ."
    },
    "sample_294": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "by Navy in",
        "sentence": "The Crimson returned to the event in 1988 and were edge , 10 -- 9 , by Navy in the opening round ."
    },
    "sample_295": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "In 1990 ,",
        "sentence": "In 1990 , Harvard won its first NCAA tournament game when it defeated Notre Dame , 9 -- 3 ."
    },
    "sample_296": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "defeated Notre Dame ,",
        "sentence": "In 1990 , Harvard won its first NCAA tournament game when it defeated Notre Dame , 9 -- 3 ."
    },
    "sample_297": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "by North Carolina .",
        "sentence": "In the quarterfinals , the Crimson were beaten handily , 18 -- 3 , by North Carolina ."
    },
    "sample_298": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in 1996 ,",
        "sentence": "Harvard returned to the quarterfinals in 1996 , after beating Hofstra , 15 -- 12 , and then fell to eventual national runners-up Virginia , 23 -- 12 ."
    },
    "sample_299": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "beating Hofstra ,",
        "sentence": "Harvard returned to the quarterfinals in 1996 , after beating Hofstra , 15 -- 12 , and then fell to eventual national runners-up Virginia , 23 -- 12 ."
    },
    "sample_300": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "runners-up Virginia ,",
        "sentence": "Harvard returned to the quarterfinals in 1996 , after beating Hofstra , 15 -- 12 , and then fell to eventual national runners-up Virginia , 23 -- 12 ."
    },
    "sample_301": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the 2006 first",
        "sentence": "They were beaten in the 2006 first round by Syracuse"
    },
    "sample_302": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "by Syracuse <UNK>",
        "sentence": "They were beaten in the 2006 first round by Syracuse"
    },
    "sample_303": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "( Turkish :",
        "sentence": "<UNK> or General Inspectorates ( Turkish : <UNK> <UNK> ) was a regional governorship whose authorities prevailed over civilian , military and judicial institutions under their domain of the direct"
    },
    "sample_304": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of Mustafa Kemal in",
        "sentence": "<UNK> or General Inspectorates ( Turkish : <UNK> <UNK> ) was a regional governorship whose authorities prevailed over civilian , military and judicial institutions under their domain of the direct"
    },
    "sample_305": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
