{
    "sample_0": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> NEW YORK --",
        "sentence": "NEW YORK -- Stocks finished an erratic session mixed Tuesday as higher commodity prices lifted energy and materials shares ."
    },
    "sample_1": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the New York Stock Exchange and",
        "sentence": "Major stock indexes had their third straight advance , reaching new 13-month highs , but there were more declining shares than advancers on the New York Stock Exchange and the"
    },
    "sample_2": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the Nasdaq Stock Market .",
        "sentence": "Major stock indexes had their third straight advance , reaching new 13-month highs , but there were more declining shares than advancers on the New York Stock Exchange and the"
    },
    "sample_3": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of U.S. exporters",
        "sentence": "An eight-month weakening of the dollar has been lifting commodities prices and shares of U.S. exporters , which benefit from stronger foreign demand for their goods when the dollar falls"
    },
    "sample_4": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Home Depot Inc. ,",
        "sentence": "Home Depot Inc. , Saks Inc. and Target Corp. all reported better-than-expected third-quarter results but also said they remain cautious ahead of the holiday shopping season . \""
    },
    "sample_5": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Saks Inc. and",
        "sentence": "Home Depot Inc. , Saks Inc. and Target Corp. all reported better-than-expected third-quarter results but also said they remain cautious ahead of the holiday shopping season . \""
    },
    "sample_6": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Target Corp. all",
        "sentence": "Home Depot Inc. , Saks Inc. and Target Corp. all reported better-than-expected third-quarter results but also said they remain cautious ahead of the holiday shopping season . \""
    },
    "sample_7": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "at ING Investment Management in",
        "sentence": "Despite the dramatic rally in the stock market , we still see the consumer operating at recessionary levels , \" said Uri Landesman , chief equity strategist and senior portfolio"
    },
    "sample_8": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in New York .",
        "sentence": "Despite the dramatic rally in the stock market , we still see the consumer operating at recessionary levels , \" said Uri Landesman , chief equity strategist and senior portfolio"
    },
    "sample_9": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> The Fed said",
        "sentence": "The Fed said output at the nation 's factories , mines and utilities rose 0.1 percent in October , less than the 0.4 percent predicted by economists polled by Thomson"
    },
    "sample_10": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "by Thomson Reuters .",
        "sentence": "The Fed said output at the nation 's factories , mines and utilities rose 0.1 percent in October , less than the 0.4 percent predicted by economists polled by Thomson"
    },
    "sample_11": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "The Labor Department 's",
        "sentence": "The Labor Department 's Producer Price Index , which measures inflation at the wholesale level , rose less than expected in October ."
    },
    "sample_12": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "'s Producer Price Index ,",
        "sentence": "The Labor Department 's Producer Price Index , which measures inflation at the wholesale level , rose less than expected in October ."
    },
    "sample_13": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "at Oklahoma City -",
        "sentence": "The market is saying inflation is not an issue , \" said Tim Courtney , chief investment officer at Oklahoma City - based Burns Advisory Group ."
    },
    "sample_14": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "The Dow Jones industrial average rose",
        "sentence": "The Dow Jones industrial average rose 30.46 , or 0.3 percent , to <UNK> ."
    },
    "sample_15": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the Dow and",
        "sentence": "It was the ninth gain in 10 days for the Dow and its highest close since Oct. 2 , 2008 , when it ended at <UNK> ."
    },
    "sample_16": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "broader Standard & Poor 's 500 index",
        "sentence": "The broader Standard & Poor 's 500 index rose 1.02 , or 0.1 percent , to <UNK> , while the Nasdaq composite index rose 5.93 , or 0.3 percent ,"
    },
    "sample_17": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the Nasdaq composite",
        "sentence": "The broader Standard & Poor 's 500 index rose 1.02 , or 0.1 percent , to <UNK> , while the Nasdaq composite index rose 5.93 , or 0.3 percent ,"
    },
    "sample_18": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the NYSE ,",
        "sentence": "Falling stocks outpaced those that rose <UNK> on the NYSE , where volume came to 972 million shares compared with 1.1 billion Monday ."
    },
    "sample_19": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "The Dow is",
        "sentence": "The Dow is up 725 points , or 7.5 percent , this month ."
    },
    "sample_20": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the New York Mercantile Exchange .",
        "sentence": "Oil rose 24 cents to settle at $ 79.14 per barrel on the New York Mercantile Exchange ."
    },
    "sample_21": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Exxon Mobil Corp. rose",
        "sentence": "Among energy and materials stocks , Exxon Mobil Corp. rose 60 cents to $ 75.03 , while United States Steel Corp. rose 93 cents , or 2.3 percent , to"
    },
    "sample_22": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "while United States Steel Corp. rose",
        "sentence": "Among energy and materials stocks , Exxon Mobil Corp. rose 60 cents to $ 75.03 , while United States Steel Corp. rose 93 cents , or 2.3 percent , to"
    },
    "sample_23": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Home Depot fell",
        "sentence": "Home Depot fell 66 cents , or 2.4 percent , to $ 26.99 , while Saks rose 26 cents , or 4.1 percent , to $ 5.67 ."
    },
    "sample_24": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "while Saks rose",
        "sentence": "Home Depot fell 66 cents , or 2.4 percent , to $ 26.99 , while Saks rose 26 cents , or 4.1 percent , to $ 5.67 ."
    },
    "sample_25": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Target fell",
        "sentence": "Target fell $ 1.52 , or 3 percent , to $ 48.77 ."
    },
    "sample_26": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Pacific Sunwear of California Inc. tumbled",
        "sentence": "Pacific Sunwear of California Inc. tumbled $ 1.13 , or 22.6 percent , to $ 3.88 after its sales forecast fell short of expectations ."
    },
    "sample_27": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "The Russell 2000 index of",
        "sentence": "The Russell 2000 index of smaller companies slipped 0.53 , or 0.1 percent , to <UNK> ."
    },
    "sample_28": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Japan 's",
        "sentence": "Overseas , Japan 's Nikkei stock average fell 0.6 percent ."
    },
    "sample_29": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "'s Nikkei stock average fell",
        "sentence": "Overseas , Japan 's Nikkei stock average fell 0.6 percent ."
    },
    "sample_30": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Britain 's",
        "sentence": "Britain 's FTSE 100 fell 0.7 percent , Germany 's DAX index fell 0.5 percent , and France 's CAC-40 lost 0.9 percent ."
    },
    "sample_31": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "'s FTSE 100 fell",
        "sentence": "Britain 's FTSE 100 fell 0.7 percent , Germany 's DAX index fell 0.5 percent , and France 's CAC-40 lost 0.9 percent ."
    },
    "sample_32": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Germany 's",
        "sentence": "Britain 's FTSE 100 fell 0.7 percent , Germany 's DAX index fell 0.5 percent , and France 's CAC-40 lost 0.9 percent ."
    },
    "sample_33": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "'s DAX index",
        "sentence": "Britain 's FTSE 100 fell 0.7 percent , Germany 's DAX index fell 0.5 percent , and France 's CAC-40 lost 0.9 percent ."
    },
    "sample_34": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and France 's",
        "sentence": "Britain 's FTSE 100 fell 0.7 percent , Germany 's DAX index fell 0.5 percent , and France 's CAC-40 lost 0.9 percent ."
    },
    "sample_35": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "'s CAC-40 lost",
        "sentence": "Britain 's FTSE 100 fell 0.7 percent , Germany 's DAX index fell 0.5 percent , and France 's CAC-40 lost 0.9 percent ."
    },
    "sample_36": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Home Depot CEO",
        "sentence": "Home Depot CEO Nardelli quits"
    },
    "sample_37": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "CEO Nardelli quits",
        "sentence": "Home Depot CEO Nardelli quits"
    },
    "sample_38": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> ATLANTA -",
        "sentence": "ATLANTA - Bob Nardelli said he had no intention of stepping down ."
    },
    "sample_39": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "- Bob Nardelli said",
        "sentence": "ATLANTA - Bob Nardelli said he had no intention of stepping down ."
    },
    "sample_40": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and The Home Depot Inc. 's",
        "sentence": "But in the end , analysts said , the criticism over Nardelli 's hefty pay and The Home Depot Inc. 's poor stock performance forced a change of heart ."
    },
    "sample_41": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Nardelli abruptly",
        "sentence": "Nardelli abruptly resigned as chairman and chief executive of the world 's largest home improvement store chain after six years at the helm , the company said Wednesday ."
    },
    "sample_42": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Atlanta -",
        "sentence": "He did n't leave empty-handed : the Atlanta - based company said Nardelli would receive a severance package worth roughly $ 210 million , an amount decried by some lawmakers"
    },
    "sample_43": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "said Nardelli would",
        "sentence": "He did n't leave empty-handed : the Atlanta - based company said Nardelli would receive a severance package worth roughly $ 210 million , an amount decried by some lawmakers"
    },
    "sample_44": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "Rep. Barney Frank ,",
        "sentence": "It 's a sign of being totally out of touch , \" said Rep. Barney Frank , D-Mass. , the incoming chairman of the House Financial Services Committee . \""
    },
    "sample_45": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the House Financial Services Committee .",
        "sentence": "It 's a sign of being totally out of touch , \" said Rep. Barney Frank , D-Mass. , the incoming chairman of the House Financial Services Committee . \""
    },
    "sample_46": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Frank said",
        "sentence": "Frank said he would push for legislation requiring public companies to allow shareholders to have a say in compensation and severance for senior executives ."
    },
    "sample_47": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "At Home Depot 's",
        "sentence": "At Home Depot 's annual meeting last May , shareholder proposals to give investors a say on the CEO 's pay and to restrict retirement benefits for senior executives were"
    },
    "sample_48": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Nardelli 's",
        "sentence": "Nardelli 's severance package includes a cash payment of $ 20 million and the acceleration of unvested deferred stock awards currently valued at roughly $ 77 million ."
    },
    "sample_49": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "A Home Depot spokesman",
        "sentence": "A Home Depot spokesman said the timing of the resignation , which was effective Tuesday , had no bearing on the amount in the package ."
    },
    "sample_50": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "million Home Depot set",
        "sentence": "The total package is seven times the $ 30 million Home Depot set aside last June for stores and employees that provide good customer service ."
    },
    "sample_51": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the United States ,",
        "sentence": "Home Depot has 2,127 stores and 355,000 employees in the United States , Canada , Mexico and China ."
    },
    "sample_52": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Canada ,",
        "sentence": "Home Depot has 2,127 stores and 355,000 employees in the United States , Canada , Mexico and China ."
    },
    "sample_53": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Mexico and",
        "sentence": "Home Depot has 2,127 stores and 355,000 employees in the United States , Canada , Mexico and China ."
    },
    "sample_54": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and China .",
        "sentence": "Home Depot has 2,127 stores and 355,000 employees in the United States , Canada , Mexico and China ."
    },
    "sample_55": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Home Depot said",
        "sentence": "Home Depot said Nardelli was being replaced by Frank Blake , its vice chairman , effective immediately ."
    },
    "sample_56": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "said Nardelli was",
        "sentence": "Home Depot said Nardelli was being replaced by Frank Blake , its vice chairman , effective immediately ."
    },
    "sample_57": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "by Frank Blake ,",
        "sentence": "Home Depot said Nardelli was being replaced by Frank Blake , its vice chairman , effective immediately ."
    },
    "sample_58": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Home Depot co-founder",
        "sentence": "Home Depot co-founder Bernie Marcus , who had a hand in hiring Nardelli , said he supports the board 's decision to replace Nardelli with Blake . \""
    },
    "sample_59": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "co-founder Bernie Marcus ,",
        "sentence": "Home Depot co-founder Bernie Marcus , who had a hand in hiring Nardelli , said he supports the board 's decision to replace Nardelli with Blake . \""
    },
    "sample_60": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "hiring Nardelli ,",
        "sentence": "Home Depot co-founder Bernie Marcus , who had a hand in hiring Nardelli , said he supports the board 's decision to replace Nardelli with Blake . \""
    },
    "sample_61": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "replace Nardelli with",
        "sentence": "Home Depot co-founder Bernie Marcus , who had a hand in hiring Nardelli , said he supports the board 's decision to replace Nardelli with Blake . \""
    },
    "sample_62": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "with Blake .",
        "sentence": "Home Depot co-founder Bernie Marcus , who had a hand in hiring Nardelli , said he supports the board 's decision to replace Nardelli with Blake . \""
    },
    "sample_63": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "said Marcus ,",
        "sentence": "My concern is what happens in the future , and I feel very good about it , \" said Marcus , who no longer works for Home Depot in any"
    },
    "sample_64": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "for Home Depot in",
        "sentence": "My concern is what happens in the future , and I feel very good about it , \" said Marcus , who no longer works for Home Depot in any"
    },
    "sample_65": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Marcus said",
        "sentence": "Asked about the severance payout , Marcus said the amount wo n't be that big a deal in the long-run if the company 's stock price improves . \""
    },
    "sample_66": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Marcus said",
        "sentence": "Marcus said ."
    },
    "sample_67": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Nardelli ,",
        "sentence": "Nardelli , a former college football player , became CEO of Home Depot in December 2000 after being passed over for the top job at General Electric Co. , where"
    },
    "sample_68": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of Home Depot in",
        "sentence": "Nardelli , a former college football player , became CEO of Home Depot in December 2000 after being passed over for the top job at General Electric Co. , where"
    },
    "sample_69": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "at General Electric Co. ,",
        "sentence": "Nardelli , a former college football player , became CEO of Home Depot in December 2000 after being passed over for the top job at General Electric Co. , where"
    },
    "sample_70": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "where Nardelli had",
        "sentence": "Nardelli , a former college football player , became CEO of Home Depot in December 2000 after being passed over for the top job at General Electric Co. , where"
    },
    "sample_71": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Blake 's",
        "sentence": "Blake 's appointment is permanent , Home Depot spokesman Jerry Shields said ."
    },
    "sample_72": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Home Depot spokesman",
        "sentence": "Blake 's appointment is permanent , Home Depot spokesman Jerry Shields said ."
    },
    "sample_73": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "make Blake available",
        "sentence": "The company declined to make Blake available for comment , and messages left for Nardelli with his secretary and on his wife 's cell phone were not immediately returned ."
    },
    "sample_74": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "for Nardelli with",
        "sentence": "The company declined to make Blake available for comment , and messages left for Nardelli with his secretary and on his wife 's cell phone were not immediately returned ."
    },
    "sample_75": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Home Depot shares",
        "sentence": "Home Depot shares rose 91 cents , or 2.3 percent , to close at $ 41.07 on the New York Stock Exchange , near the upper end of their 52-week"
    },
    "sample_76": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the New York Stock Exchange ,",
        "sentence": "Home Depot shares rose 91 cents , or 2.3 percent , to close at $ 41.07 on the New York Stock Exchange , near the upper end of their 52-week"
    },
    "sample_77": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Home Depot 's",
        "sentence": "Before Wednesday 's news , Home Depot 's stock had been down more than 3 percent on a split-adjusted basis since Nardelli took over ."
    },
    "sample_78": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "since Nardelli took",
        "sentence": "Before Wednesday 's news , Home Depot 's stock had been down more than 3 percent on a split-adjusted basis since Nardelli took over ."
    },
    "sample_79": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "told The Associated Press as",
        "sentence": "Nardelli 's sudden departure was stunning in that he told The Associated Press as recently as Sept. 1 that he had no intention of leaving , and a key director"
    },
    "sample_80": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "with Nardelli despite",
        "sentence": "Nardelli 's sudden departure was stunning in that he told The Associated Press as recently as Sept. 1 that he had no intention of leaving , and a key director"
    },
    "sample_81": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Los Angeles .",
        "sentence": "That director , Bonnie Hill , did not immediately return messages left Wednesday for her at her office in Los Angeles ."
    },
    "sample_82": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "leaving Home Depot ,",
        "sentence": "Asked in the earlier AP interview if he had thought of hanging up his orange apron and leaving Home Depot , Nardelli said unequivocally that he had n't ."
    },
    "sample_83": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Nardelli said",
        "sentence": "Asked in the earlier AP interview if he had thought of hanging up his orange apron and leaving Home Depot , Nardelli said unequivocally that he had n't ."
    },
    "sample_84": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "The Home Depot ?",
        "sentence": "For The Home Depot ? \""
    },
    "sample_85": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Marcus said",
        "sentence": "Marcus said he had no idea Nardelli 's resignation was coming . \""
    },
    "sample_86": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "idea Nardelli 's",
        "sentence": "Marcus said he had no idea Nardelli 's resignation was coming . \""
    },
    "sample_87": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Nardelli 's",
        "sentence": "Obviously , something happened over this last period of time that changed their mind and Nardelli 's mind about staying , \" Marcus said ."
    },
    "sample_88": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "\" Marcus said",
        "sentence": "Obviously , something happened over this last period of time that changed their mind and Nardelli 's mind about staying , \" Marcus said ."
    },
    "sample_89": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Home Depot said",
        "sentence": "Home Depot said Nardelli 's decision to resign was by mutual agreement with Home Depot . \""
    },
    "sample_90": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "said Nardelli 's",
        "sentence": "Home Depot said Nardelli 's decision to resign was by mutual agreement with Home Depot . \""
    },
    "sample_91": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "with Home Depot .",
        "sentence": "Home Depot said Nardelli 's decision to resign was by mutual agreement with Home Depot . \""
    },
    "sample_92": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "to Bob for",
        "sentence": "We are very grateful to Bob for his strong leadership of The Home Depot over the past six years , \" Home Depot 's board said in a statement ."
    },
    "sample_93": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of The Home Depot over",
        "sentence": "We are very grateful to Bob for his strong leadership of The Home Depot over the past six years , \" Home Depot 's board said in a statement ."
    },
    "sample_94": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Nardelli was",
        "sentence": "Nardelli was a nuts-and-bolts leader ."
    },
    "sample_95": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "at Home Depot and",
        "sentence": "He helped increase revenue and profits at Home Depot and increase the number of stores the company operates ."
    },
    "sample_96": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Nardelli had",
        "sentence": "As of the end of 2005 , Nardelli had earned $ 123.7 million in compensation excluding certain stock option grants since becoming CEO ."
    },
    "sample_97": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Blake 's",
        "sentence": "Industry experts and analysts said his departure and Blake 's ascent to the top job are a good thing for Home Depot . \""
    },
    "sample_98": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "at Georgia State University .",
        "sentence": "This is not about strategy or vision , \" said James Senn , director of Robinson College 's Center for Global Business Leadership at Georgia State University . \""
    },
    "sample_99": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Bob has",
        "sentence": "Bob has run into some problems there ."
    },
    "sample_100": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Edward Jones analyst",
        "sentence": "Edward Jones analyst Stephanie Hoff said she views the developments at Home Depot as a sign that there was a need for change at the top , not a change"
    },
    "sample_101": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Timberlake ,",
        "sentence": "Timberlake , Diaz reportedly break up"
    },
    "sample_102": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Diaz reportedly",
        "sentence": "Timberlake , Diaz reportedly break up"
    },
    "sample_103": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "Former N ' Sync singer",
        "sentence": "Former N ' Sync singer seeing former flame , magazine reports"
    },
    "sample_104": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Justin Timberlake and",
        "sentence": "Justin Timberlake and Cameron Diaz have called it quits , according to a report in Star magazine ."
    },
    "sample_105": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Cameron Diaz have",
        "sentence": "Justin Timberlake and Cameron Diaz have called it quits , according to a report in Star magazine ."
    },
    "sample_106": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Star magazine .",
        "sentence": "Justin Timberlake and Cameron Diaz have called it quits , according to a report in Star magazine ."
    },
    "sample_107": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "to Star ,",
        "sentence": "According to Star , Diaz , 34 , spent Christmas with her family in Vail , Colo. , while Timberlake , 25 , was with his family near Memphis ."
    },
    "sample_108": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Diaz ,",
        "sentence": "According to Star , Diaz , 34 , spent Christmas with her family in Vail , Colo. , while Timberlake , 25 , was with his family near Memphis ."
    },
    "sample_109": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "spent Christmas with",
        "sentence": "According to Star , Diaz , 34 , spent Christmas with her family in Vail , Colo. , while Timberlake , 25 , was with his family near Memphis ."
    },
    "sample_110": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Vail ,",
        "sentence": "According to Star , Diaz , 34 , spent Christmas with her family in Vail , Colo. , while Timberlake , 25 , was with his family near Memphis ."
    },
    "sample_111": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Colo. ,",
        "sentence": "According to Star , Diaz , 34 , spent Christmas with her family in Vail , Colo. , while Timberlake , 25 , was with his family near Memphis ."
    },
    "sample_112": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "while Timberlake ,",
        "sentence": "According to Star , Diaz , 34 , spent Christmas with her family in Vail , Colo. , while Timberlake , 25 , was with his family near Memphis ."
    },
    "sample_113": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "near Memphis .",
        "sentence": "According to Star , Diaz , 34 , spent Christmas with her family in Vail , Colo. , while Timberlake , 25 , was with his family near Memphis ."
    },
    "sample_114": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "former N ' Sync singer",
        "sentence": "The magazine quotes a source who says the former N ' Sync singer told friends that he and the actress had broken up ."
    },
    "sample_115": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "\" Saturday Night Live .",
        "sentence": "The couple were last seen together on Dec. 16 when she introduced his musical performance on \" Saturday Night Live . \""
    },
    "sample_116": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Diaz and",
        "sentence": "Diaz and Timberlake started dating shortly after they met each other at the 2003 Kids ' Choice Awards ."
    },
    "sample_117": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Timberlake started",
        "sentence": "Diaz and Timberlake started dating shortly after they met each other at the 2003 Kids ' Choice Awards ."
    },
    "sample_118": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "2003 Kids ' Choice Awards .",
        "sentence": "Diaz and Timberlake started dating shortly after they met each other at the 2003 Kids ' Choice Awards ."
    },
    "sample_119": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "that Timberlake has",
        "sentence": "The magazine also reported that Timberlake has started seeing a former flame , Veronica Finn ."
    },
    "sample_120": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Veronica Finn .",
        "sentence": "The magazine also reported that Timberlake has started seeing a former flame , Veronica Finn ."
    },
    "sample_121": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "dating Britney Spears .",
        "sentence": "The pair dated in the late '90s before he began dating Britney Spears ."
    },
    "sample_122": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Finn and",
        "sentence": "Finn and Spears were briefly in a girl group together called Innosense , according to music impresario Lou Pearlman ."
    },
    "sample_123": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Spears were",
        "sentence": "Finn and Spears were briefly in a girl group together called Innosense , according to music impresario Lou Pearlman ."
    },
    "sample_124": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "called Innosense ,",
        "sentence": "Finn and Spears were briefly in a girl group together called Innosense , according to music impresario Lou Pearlman ."
    },
    "sample_125": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "impresario Lou Pearlman .",
        "sentence": "Finn and Spears were briefly in a girl group together called Innosense , according to music impresario Lou Pearlman ."
    },
    "sample_126": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Barbara Walters stands",
        "sentence": "Barbara Walters stands by Rosie O'Donnell '"
    },
    "sample_127": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "by Rosie O'Donnell '",
        "sentence": "Barbara Walters stands by Rosie O'Donnell '"
    },
    "sample_128": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "denies Trump 's",
        "sentence": "View ' host denies Trump 's claim she wanted comedian off morning show"
    },
    "sample_129": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> NEW YORK -",
        "sentence": "NEW YORK - Barbara Walters is back from vacation -- and she 's standing by Rosie O'Donnell in her bitter battle of words with Donald Trump ."
    },
    "sample_130": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "- Barbara Walters is",
        "sentence": "NEW YORK - Barbara Walters is back from vacation -- and she 's standing by Rosie O'Donnell in her bitter battle of words with Donald Trump ."
    },
    "sample_131": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "by Rosie O'Donnell in",
        "sentence": "NEW YORK - Barbara Walters is back from vacation -- and she 's standing by Rosie O'Donnell in her bitter battle of words with Donald Trump ."
    },
    "sample_132": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "with Donald Trump .",
        "sentence": "NEW YORK - Barbara Walters is back from vacation -- and she 's standing by Rosie O'Donnell in her bitter battle of words with Donald Trump ."
    },
    "sample_133": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Walters ,",
        "sentence": "Walters , creator of ABC 's \" The View , \" said Wednesday on the daytime chat show that she never told Trump she did n't want O'Donnell on the"
    },
    "sample_134": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of ABC 's",
        "sentence": "Walters , creator of ABC 's \" The View , \" said Wednesday on the daytime chat show that she never told Trump she did n't want O'Donnell on the"
    },
    "sample_135": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "\" The View ,",
        "sentence": "Walters , creator of ABC 's \" The View , \" said Wednesday on the daytime chat show that she never told Trump she did n't want O'Donnell on the"
    },
    "sample_136": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "told Trump she",
        "sentence": "Walters , creator of ABC 's \" The View , \" said Wednesday on the daytime chat show that she never told Trump she did n't want O'Donnell on the"
    },
    "sample_137": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "want O'Donnell on",
        "sentence": "Walters , creator of ABC 's \" The View , \" said Wednesday on the daytime chat show that she never told Trump she did n't want O'Donnell on the"
    },
    "sample_138": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "\" Walters said",
        "sentence": "She has brought a new vitality to this show and the ratings prove it , \" Walters said of O'Donnell , who is on vacation this week ."
    },
    "sample_139": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of O'Donnell ,",
        "sentence": "She has brought a new vitality to this show and the ratings prove it , \" Walters said of O'Donnell , who is on vacation this week ."
    },
    "sample_140": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Walters said",
        "sentence": "When she returns , Walters said , \" We will all welcome her back with open arms . \""
    },
    "sample_141": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Walters also",
        "sentence": "Walters also took a moment to smooth things over with The Donald , who got all riled up when O'Donnell said on \" The View \" that he had been"
    },
    "sample_142": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "with The Donald ,",
        "sentence": "Walters also took a moment to smooth things over with The Donald , who got all riled up when O'Donnell said on \" The View \" that he had been"
    },
    "sample_143": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "when O'Donnell said",
        "sentence": "Walters also took a moment to smooth things over with The Donald , who got all riled up when O'Donnell said on \" The View \" that he had been"
    },
    "sample_144": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "\" The View \"",
        "sentence": "Walters also took a moment to smooth things over with The Donald , who got all riled up when O'Donnell said on \" The View \" that he had been"
    },
    "sample_145": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> ABC has",
        "sentence": "ABC has asked me to say this just to clarify things , and I will quote : ' Donald Trump has never filed for personal bankruptcy ."
    },
    "sample_146": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "' Donald Trump has",
        "sentence": "ABC has asked me to say this just to clarify things , and I will quote : ' Donald Trump has never filed for personal bankruptcy ."
    },
    "sample_147": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "' Walters said",
        "sentence": "They are out of bankruptcy now , \" ' Walters said ."
    },
    "sample_148": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "with The Associated Press ,",
        "sentence": "In a phone interview with The Associated Press , Trump said he appreciated that Walters \" did a retraction \" and claimed the show 's \" ratings are up because"
    },
    "sample_149": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Trump said",
        "sentence": "In a phone interview with The Associated Press , Trump said he appreciated that Walters \" did a retraction \" and claimed the show 's \" ratings are up because"
    },
    "sample_150": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "that Walters \"",
        "sentence": "In a phone interview with The Associated Press , Trump said he appreciated that Walters \" did a retraction \" and claimed the show 's \" ratings are up because"
    },
    "sample_151": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Barbara fully",
        "sentence": "Barbara fully understands what Barbara told me , \" he said . \""
    },
    "sample_152": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "what Barbara told",
        "sentence": "Barbara fully understands what Barbara told me , \" he said . \""
    },
    "sample_153": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "because Rosie 's",
        "sentence": "I mean , that thing will explode because Rosie 's wacko . \""
    },
    "sample_154": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> O'Donnell and",
        "sentence": "O'Donnell and Trump have been feuding since he announced last month that Miss USA Tara Conner , whose title had been in jeopardy because of underage drinking , would keep"
    },
    "sample_155": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Trump have",
        "sentence": "O'Donnell and Trump have been feuding since he announced last month that Miss USA Tara Conner , whose title had been in jeopardy because of underage drinking , would keep"
    },
    "sample_156": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "that Miss USA Tara",
        "sentence": "O'Donnell and Trump have been feuding since he announced last month that Miss USA Tara Conner , whose title had been in jeopardy because of underage drinking , would keep"
    },
    "sample_157": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "USA Tara Conner ,",
        "sentence": "O'Donnell and Trump have been feuding since he announced last month that Miss USA Tara Conner , whose title had been in jeopardy because of underage drinking , would keep"
    },
    "sample_158": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Trump is",
        "sentence": "Trump is the owner of the Miss Universe Organization , which includes Miss USA and Miss Teen USA ."
    },
    "sample_159": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the Miss Universe Organization ,",
        "sentence": "Trump is the owner of the Miss Universe Organization , which includes Miss USA and Miss Teen USA ."
    },
    "sample_160": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "includes Miss USA and",
        "sentence": "Trump is the owner of the Miss Universe Organization , which includes Miss USA and Miss Teen USA ."
    },
    "sample_161": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Miss Teen USA .",
        "sentence": "Trump is the owner of the Miss Universe Organization , which includes Miss USA and Miss Teen USA ."
    },
    "sample_162": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "\" The View ,",
        "sentence": "The 44-year-old outspoken moderator of \" The View , \" who joined the show in September , said Trump 's news conference with Conner had annoyed her \" on a"
    },
    "sample_163": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "said Trump 's",
        "sentence": "The 44-year-old outspoken moderator of \" The View , \" who joined the show in September , said Trump 's news conference with Conner had annoyed her \" on a"
    },
    "sample_164": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "with Conner had",
        "sentence": "The 44-year-old outspoken moderator of \" The View , \" who joined the show in September , said Trump 's news conference with Conner had annoyed her \" on a"
    },
    "sample_165": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in America .",
        "sentence": "The 44-year-old outspoken moderator of \" The View , \" who joined the show in September , said Trump 's news conference with Conner had annoyed her \" on a"
    },
    "sample_166": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Trump fired",
        "sentence": "Trump fired back , calling O'Donnell a \" loser \" and a \" bully , \" among other insults , in various media interviews ."
    },
    "sample_167": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "calling O'Donnell a",
        "sentence": "Trump fired back , calling O'Donnell a \" loser \" and a \" bully , \" among other insults , in various media interviews ."
    },
    "sample_168": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of NBC 's",
        "sentence": "He is the host of NBC 's \" The Apprentice , \" which begins its new season Sunday ."
    },
    "sample_169": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "\" The Apprentice ,",
        "sentence": "He is the host of NBC 's \" The Apprentice , \" which begins its new season Sunday ."
    },
    "sample_170": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "\" Santa Baby \"",
        "sentence": "The resolution list goes on and on -- much like that interminable karaoke version of \" Santa Baby \" at this year 's holiday party ."
    },
    "sample_171": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Mayo Clinic found",
        "sentence": "Also , a recent study by the Mayo Clinic found that women 's bodies are less adept at breaking down alcohol than men 's ."
    },
    "sample_172": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "The Mayo Clinic study",
        "sentence": "The Mayo Clinic study says one drink a day is OK for \" younger women who are n't planning a pregnancy \" and that \" postmenopausal women should limit themselves"
    },
    "sample_173": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "at Stony Brook University in",
        "sentence": "Looking for a definitive answer , I turned to another study , this one conducted by a group of doctors at Stony Brook University in New York ."
    },
    "sample_174": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in New York .",
        "sentence": "Looking for a definitive answer , I turned to another study , this one conducted by a group of doctors at Stony Brook University in New York ."
    },
    "sample_175": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Goteborg University in",
        "sentence": "Or should I listen to the doctors the Goteborg University in Sweden , who found that mice that had ingested low levels of alcohol on a daily basis showed a"
    },
    "sample_176": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Sweden ,",
        "sentence": "Or should I listen to the doctors the Goteborg University in Sweden , who found that mice that had ingested low levels of alcohol on a daily basis showed a"
    },
    "sample_177": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "In London ,",
        "sentence": "In London , researchers found that people who drank alcohol have a lower risk of developing non - Hodgkin 's lymphoma , but the risk of cancer of the mouth"
    },
    "sample_178": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "- Hodgkin 's lymphoma ,",
        "sentence": "In London , researchers found that people who drank alcohol have a lower risk of developing non - Hodgkin 's lymphoma , but the risk of cancer of the mouth"
    },
    "sample_179": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "At Ohio State University ,",
        "sentence": "At Ohio State University , a study showed that drinking moderately ( such as a couple of drinks a day ) improved the memories of laboratory rats , although a"
    },
    "sample_180": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the University of Missouri declared",
        "sentence": "At Ohio State University , a study showed that drinking moderately ( such as a couple of drinks a day ) improved the memories of laboratory rats , although a"
    },
    "sample_181": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> BIRMINGHAM ,",
        "sentence": "BIRMINGHAM , Ala. - For years , Al Rohling watched parents quit their jobs when their kids got sick , deliberately making their incomes drop to a point where they"
    },
    "sample_182": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Ala. -",
        "sentence": "BIRMINGHAM , Ala. - For years , Al Rohling watched parents quit their jobs when their kids got sick , deliberately making their incomes drop to a point where they"
    },
    "sample_183": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "get U.S. government medical",
        "sentence": "BIRMINGHAM , Ala. - For years , Al Rohling watched parents quit their jobs when their kids got sick , deliberately making their incomes drop to a point where they"
    },
    "sample_184": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "directed Alabama 's",
        "sentence": "Rohling , who directed Alabama 's housing authority at the time , reached a startling conclusion : If children could drive parents into hardship when they became ill , could"
    },
    "sample_185": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Blue Cross and Blue Shield of Alabama health",
        "sentence": "Rohling quit his job in 1988 to help set up the Child Caring Foundation , which provides free health insurance for children through the Blue Cross and Blue Shield of"
    },
    "sample_186": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "between Medicaid --",
        "sentence": "The foundation is just one example of a charity that bridges the gap between Medicaid -- subsidized insurance -- for the poorest and private health insurance paid for either privately"
    },
    "sample_187": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "million U.S. children",
        "sentence": "That gap leaves up to 9 million U.S. children uninsured in the United States , a nation with no universal health care ."
    },
    "sample_188": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the United States ,",
        "sentence": "That gap leaves up to 9 million U.S. children uninsured in the United States , a nation with no universal health care ."
    },
    "sample_189": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "a Washington -",
        "sentence": "The problem of the uninsured is getting worse , \" and the number of uninsured children has risen since 2004 , said Jennifer Tolbert , principal analyst with the Kaiser"
    },
    "sample_190": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the U.S. Congress could",
        "sentence": "Tolbert said it was possible the U.S. Congress could increase the scope of the State Children 's Health Insurance Program ( SCHIP ) to provide greater state coverage for uninsured"
    },
    "sample_191": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the State Children 's Health Insurance Program (",
        "sentence": "Tolbert said it was possible the U.S. Congress could increase the scope of the State Children 's Health Insurance Program ( SCHIP ) to provide greater state coverage for uninsured"
    },
    "sample_192": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "( SCHIP )",
        "sentence": "Tolbert said it was possible the U.S. Congress could increase the scope of the State Children 's Health Insurance Program ( SCHIP ) to provide greater state coverage for uninsured"
    },
    "sample_193": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "In Alabama ,",
        "sentence": "In Alabama , there were 230,000 uninsured children in 1988 , and that has fallen to around 70,000 due to a combination of the Child Caring Foundation and state programs"
    },
    "sample_194": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "told Reuters .",
        "sentence": "With no insurance , it 's thousands of dollars just like that , \" Sharp told Reuters ."
    },
    "sample_195": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Alabama Blue Cross Blue Shield program",
        "sentence": "During their two years in the Alabama Blue Cross Blue Shield program , Sharp 's children received free medical care and she found a job working with special needs children"
    },
    "sample_196": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the University of Alabama at Birmingham School",
        "sentence": "To recruit families , Rohling tours the state presenting health screenings at schools with the help of volunteers from the University of Alabama at Birmingham School of Nursing and elsewhere"
    },
    "sample_197": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "Birmingham School of Nursing and",
        "sentence": "To recruit families , Rohling tours the state presenting health screenings at schools with the help of volunteers from the University of Alabama at Birmingham School of Nursing and elsewhere"
    },
    "sample_198": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Pittsburgh in",
        "sentence": "Low cost health insurance for low income American children began in Pittsburgh in 1985 when Highmark Blue Cross Blue Shield of Western Pennsylvania insured children of laid-off steel workers ."
    },
    "sample_199": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "when Highmark Blue Cross Blue Shield of",
        "sentence": "Low cost health insurance for low income American children began in Pittsburgh in 1985 when Highmark Blue Cross Blue Shield of Western Pennsylvania insured children of laid-off steel workers ."
    },
    "sample_200": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of Western Pennsylvania insured",
        "sentence": "Low cost health insurance for low income American children began in Pittsburgh in 1985 when Highmark Blue Cross Blue Shield of Western Pennsylvania insured children of laid-off steel workers ."
    },
    "sample_201": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of Highmark .",
        "sentence": "And the whole thing came about as an answer for how health insurance should work , \" said spokesperson Denise Grabner of Highmark ."
    },
    "sample_202": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "when Congress enacted",
        "sentence": "In 1997 , the program expanded to include children of the working poor when Congress enacted the SCHIP providing some matching funding ."
    },
    "sample_203": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the SCHIP providing",
        "sentence": "In 1997 , the program expanded to include children of the working poor when Congress enacted the SCHIP providing some matching funding ."
    },
    "sample_204": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Alabama was",
        "sentence": "Alabama was the first of 20 states to participate , creating the All Kids program , with money from state settlement with tobacco companies ."
    },
    "sample_205": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "for Medicaid .",
        "sentence": "The program provides insurance for children above the level at which they would qualify for Medicaid ."
    },
    "sample_206": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> TUSCALOOSA ,",
        "sentence": "TUSCALOOSA , Ala. - Nick Saban could n't escape his college roots , so he quit trying ."
    },
    "sample_207": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Ala. -",
        "sentence": "TUSCALOOSA , Ala. - Nick Saban could n't escape his college roots , so he quit trying ."
    },
    "sample_208": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "- Nick Saban could",
        "sentence": "TUSCALOOSA , Ala. - Nick Saban could n't escape his college roots , so he quit trying ."
    },
    "sample_209": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Saban was",
        "sentence": "Saban was introduced as Alabama 's coach on Thursday , touting his championship aspirations and citing his love of college football as a reason for taking a pay cut to"
    },
    "sample_210": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "as Alabama 's",
        "sentence": "Saban was introduced as Alabama 's coach on Thursday , touting his championship aspirations and citing his love of college football as a reason for taking a pay cut to"
    },
    "sample_211": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Miami Dolphins .",
        "sentence": "Saban was introduced as Alabama 's coach on Thursday , touting his championship aspirations and citing his love of college football as a reason for taking a pay cut to"
    },
    "sample_212": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "things Crimson Tide fans",
        "sentence": "In other words , he said the things Crimson Tide fans most wanted to hear . \""
    },
    "sample_213": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "coach Bear Bryant ,",
        "sentence": "Taking over a program with a rich tradition led by the late coach Bear Bryant , who won five national titles , Saban refused to dwell in the past ."
    },
    "sample_214": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Saban refused",
        "sentence": "Taking over a program with a rich tradition led by the late coach Bear Bryant , who won five national titles , Saban refused to dwell in the past ."
    },
    "sample_215": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "thing Alabama fans",
        "sentence": "His resume features the one thing Alabama fans hunger for most : A national title ."
    },
    "sample_216": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "director Mal Moore put",
        "sentence": "His \" championship credentials \" -- as athletic director Mal Moore put it -- are why the Tide was willing to offer a reported eight-year deal worth an estimated $"
    },
    "sample_217": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Tide was",
        "sentence": "His \" championship credentials \" -- as athletic director Mal Moore put it -- are why the Tide was willing to offer a reported eight-year deal worth an estimated $"
    },
    "sample_218": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "\" Saban said",
        "sentence": "I know there 's tremendous expectations here , \" Saban said . \""
    },
    "sample_219": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Saban led",
        "sentence": "Saban led Alabama divisional rival LSU to a national title in 2003 and two SEC championships before heading to Miami ."
    },
    "sample_220": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "led Alabama divisional",
        "sentence": "Saban led Alabama divisional rival LSU to a national title in 2003 and two SEC championships before heading to Miami ."
    },
    "sample_221": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "rival LSU to",
        "sentence": "Saban led Alabama divisional rival LSU to a national title in 2003 and two SEC championships before heading to Miami ."
    },
    "sample_222": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "two SEC championships",
        "sentence": "Saban led Alabama divisional rival LSU to a national title in 2003 and two SEC championships before heading to Miami ."
    },
    "sample_223": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "to Miami .",
        "sentence": "Saban led Alabama divisional rival LSU to a national title in 2003 and two SEC championships before heading to Miami ."
    },
    "sample_224": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Alabama has",
        "sentence": "Alabama has n't won the league or even the Western Division since 1999 under Mike DuBose ."
    },
    "sample_225": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "under Mike DuBose .",
        "sentence": "Alabama has n't won the league or even the Western Division since 1999 under Mike DuBose ."
    },
    "sample_226": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "The Tide 's",
        "sentence": "The Tide 's latest national title -- its sixth -- came in 1992 under Gene Stallings ."
    },
    "sample_227": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "under Gene Stallings .",
        "sentence": "The Tide 's latest national title -- its sixth -- came in 1992 under Gene Stallings ."
    },
    "sample_228": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Alabama has",
        "sentence": "Alabama has had four losing seasons since ' 97 . \""
    },
    "sample_229": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "said Moore ,",
        "sentence": "His teams always play with confidence and pride and I know that in order to win a national championship , a team has to be mentally as well as physically"
    },
    "sample_230": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "under Bryant .",
        "sentence": "His teams always play with confidence and pride and I know that in order to win a national championship , a team has to be mentally as well as physically"
    },
    "sample_231": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "Coach Saban 's",
        "sentence": "Coach Saban 's teams have always possessed those qualities . \""
    },
    "sample_232": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Moore said",
        "sentence": "As for the big salary , Moore said , \" I just think it was a very crucial hire for us in this time in our history . \""
    },
    "sample_233": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Alabama was",
        "sentence": "Not everyone in Alabama was convinced . \""
    },
    "sample_234": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "like Saban would",
        "sentence": "Vincent said having a high-profile coach like Saban would create more interest in the University of Alabama , which would bring more interest and money to the academic side ."
    },
    "sample_235": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the University of Alabama ,",
        "sentence": "Vincent said having a high-profile coach like Saban would create more interest in the University of Alabama , which would bring more interest and money to the academic side ."
    },
    "sample_236": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Saban said",
        "sentence": "Saban said his first goals were to hire a coaching staff and work on completing the Tide 's recruiting class ."
    },
    "sample_237": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Tide 's",
        "sentence": "Saban said his first goals were to hire a coaching staff and work on completing the Tide 's recruiting class ."
    },
    "sample_238": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "hired Florida State assistant",
        "sentence": "He has already hired Florida State assistant Kevin Steele to be his defensive coordinator , according to Seminoles coach Bobby Bowden ."
    },
    "sample_239": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "assistant Kevin Steele to",
        "sentence": "He has already hired Florida State assistant Kevin Steele to be his defensive coordinator , according to Seminoles coach Bobby Bowden ."
    },
    "sample_240": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "to Seminoles coach",
        "sentence": "He has already hired Florida State assistant Kevin Steele to be his defensive coordinator , according to Seminoles coach Bobby Bowden ."
    },
    "sample_241": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "coach Bobby Bowden .",
        "sentence": "He has already hired Florida State assistant Kevin Steele to be his defensive coordinator , according to Seminoles coach Bobby Bowden ."
    },
    "sample_242": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Saban 's",
        "sentence": "Saban 's success attracting top prep players is evident ."
    },
    "sample_243": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Quarterback JaMarcus",
        "sentence": "Quarterback JaMarcus Russell , receiver Early Doucet and safety LaRon Landry -- who all played key roles in LSU 's 41-14 Sugar Bowl victory over Notre Dame on Wednesday night"
    },
    "sample_244": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "Quarterback JaMarcus Russell ,",
        "sentence": "Quarterback JaMarcus Russell , receiver Early Doucet and safety LaRon Landry -- who all played key roles in LSU 's 41-14 Sugar Bowl victory over Notre Dame on Wednesday night"
    },
    "sample_245": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "receiver Early Doucet and",
        "sentence": "Quarterback JaMarcus Russell , receiver Early Doucet and safety LaRon Landry -- who all played key roles in LSU 's 41-14 Sugar Bowl victory over Notre Dame on Wednesday night"
    },
    "sample_246": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "safety LaRon Landry --",
        "sentence": "Quarterback JaMarcus Russell , receiver Early Doucet and safety LaRon Landry -- who all played key roles in LSU 's 41-14 Sugar Bowl victory over Notre Dame on Wednesday night"
    },
    "sample_247": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in LSU 's",
        "sentence": "Quarterback JaMarcus Russell , receiver Early Doucet and safety LaRon Landry -- who all played key roles in LSU 's 41-14 Sugar Bowl victory over Notre Dame on Wednesday night"
    },
    "sample_248": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "41-14 Sugar Bowl victory",
        "sentence": "Quarterback JaMarcus Russell , receiver Early Doucet and safety LaRon Landry -- who all played key roles in LSU 's 41-14 Sugar Bowl victory over Notre Dame on Wednesday night"
    },
    "sample_249": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "over Notre Dame on",
        "sentence": "Quarterback JaMarcus Russell , receiver Early Doucet and safety LaRon Landry -- who all played key roles in LSU 's 41-14 Sugar Bowl victory over Notre Dame on Wednesday night"
    },
    "sample_250": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "to Baton Rouge .",
        "sentence": "Quarterback JaMarcus Russell , receiver Early Doucet and safety LaRon Landry -- who all played key roles in LSU 's 41-14 Sugar Bowl victory over Notre Dame on Wednesday night"
    },
    "sample_251": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Saban 's",
        "sentence": "Saban 's wife , Terry , encouraged the move to Tuscaloosa and another college job . \""
    },
    "sample_252": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "to Tuscaloosa and",
        "sentence": "Saban 's wife , Terry , encouraged the move to Tuscaloosa and another college job . \""
    },
    "sample_253": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Saban said",
        "sentence": "Saban said when he arrived at LSU from Michigan State as a less well-known coach , it was just him , an equipment manager and his agent ."
    },
    "sample_254": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "at LSU from",
        "sentence": "Saban said when he arrived at LSU from Michigan State as a less well-known coach , it was just him , an equipment manager and his agent ."
    },
    "sample_255": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "from Michigan State as",
        "sentence": "Saban said when he arrived at LSU from Michigan State as a less well-known coach , it was just him , an equipment manager and his agent ."
    },
    "sample_256": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "well-traveled Saban also",
        "sentence": "The well-traveled Saban also said he intends for this to be his final coaching stop before retiring to Lake Burton in north Georgia , where he has a home ."
    },
    "sample_257": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "to Lake Burton in",
        "sentence": "The well-traveled Saban also said he intends for this to be his final coaching stop before retiring to Lake Burton in north Georgia , where he has a home ."
    },
    "sample_258": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "north Georgia ,",
        "sentence": "The well-traveled Saban also said he intends for this to be his final coaching stop before retiring to Lake Burton in north Georgia , where he has a home ."
    },
    "sample_259": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "55-year-old Saban said",
        "sentence": "That 's where I like it , and that 's my next stop , \" the 55-year-old Saban said ."
    },
    "sample_260": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Riley to",
        "sentence": "Riley to have surgery on right knee"
    },
    "sample_261": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> MIAMI -",
        "sentence": "MIAMI - Pat Riley is taking a break from a season that has left him limping and in pain ."
    },
    "sample_262": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "- Pat Riley is",
        "sentence": "MIAMI - Pat Riley is taking a break from a season that has left him limping and in pain ."
    },
    "sample_263": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "The Miami Heat coach",
        "sentence": "The Miami Heat coach began an indefinite leave of absence Wednesday because of hip and knee problems , choosing assistant Ron Rothstein to fill his spot on an interim basis"
    },
    "sample_264": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "assistant Ron Rothstein to",
        "sentence": "The Miami Heat coach began an indefinite leave of absence Wednesday because of hip and knee problems , choosing assistant Ron Rothstein to fill his spot on an interim basis"
    },
    "sample_265": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Riley will",
        "sentence": "Riley will have surgery Friday to remove floating chips in his right knee ."
    },
    "sample_266": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Miami 's",
        "sentence": "Miami 's record fell to 13-18 on Wednesday after a 110-95 loss to the Los Angeles Clippers ."
    },
    "sample_267": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Los Angeles Clippers .",
        "sentence": "Miami 's record fell to 13-18 on Wednesday after a 110-95 loss to the Los Angeles Clippers ."
    },
    "sample_268": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Heat have",
        "sentence": "Already this season , the Heat have seen Shaquille O'Neal , Dwyane Wade and Jason Williams -- perhaps the three biggest keys in last year 's championship run -- miss"
    },
    "sample_269": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "seen Shaquille O'Neal ,",
        "sentence": "Already this season , the Heat have seen Shaquille O'Neal , Dwyane Wade and Jason Williams -- perhaps the three biggest keys in last year 's championship run -- miss"
    },
    "sample_270": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Dwyane Wade and",
        "sentence": "Already this season , the Heat have seen Shaquille O'Neal , Dwyane Wade and Jason Williams -- perhaps the three biggest keys in last year 's championship run -- miss"
    },
    "sample_271": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Jason Williams --",
        "sentence": "Already this season , the Heat have seen Shaquille O'Neal , Dwyane Wade and Jason Williams -- perhaps the three biggest keys in last year 's championship run -- miss"
    },
    "sample_272": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "'s Riley 's",
        "sentence": "And now it 's Riley 's turn . \""
    },
    "sample_273": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "\" Riley said",
        "sentence": "We have a championship team that is sideways right now , so this is going to be a great challenge , \" Riley said . \""
    },
    "sample_274": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Riley ,",
        "sentence": "Riley , who also is the Heat president , resigned as coach shortly before the 2003-04 season , then returned to the bench in December 2005 , replacing Stan Van"
    },
    "sample_275": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Heat president",
        "sentence": "Riley , who also is the Heat president , resigned as coach shortly before the 2003-04 season , then returned to the bench in December 2005 , replacing Stan Van"
    },
    "sample_276": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "replacing Stan Van Gundy and",
        "sentence": "Riley , who also is the Heat president , resigned as coach shortly before the 2003-04 season , then returned to the bench in December 2005 , replacing Stan Van"
    },
    "sample_277": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Riley said",
        "sentence": "In September , after deciding against having offseason surgery , Riley said he did n't expect to need the operation this season , but the pain has apparently worsened in"
    },
    "sample_278": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "\" Riley said",
        "sentence": "I 'm just tired of the pain and the medication , \" Riley said ."
    },
    "sample_279": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Riley was",
        "sentence": "Riley was asked if the knee injury , or at its severity , stems in any way from him reportedly kicking a locker room door last week following a loss"
    },
    "sample_280": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Chicago .",
        "sentence": "Riley was asked if the knee injury , or at its severity , stems in any way from him reportedly kicking a locker room door last week following a loss"
    },
    "sample_281": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "\" Riley said",
        "sentence": "What I do in the locker room really has always been my business , \" Riley said ."
    },
    "sample_282": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Heat center",
        "sentence": "Heat center Alonzo Mourning said he did n't know if the kick made Riley 's condition worse . \""
    },
    "sample_283": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "center Alonzo Mourning said",
        "sentence": "Heat center Alonzo Mourning said he did n't know if the kick made Riley 's condition worse . \""
    },
    "sample_284": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "made Riley 's",
        "sentence": "Heat center Alonzo Mourning said he did n't know if the kick made Riley 's condition worse . \""
    },
    "sample_285": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "\" Mourning said",
        "sentence": "Typical Riles , \" Mourning said . \""
    },
    "sample_286": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Rothstein was",
        "sentence": "Rothstein was the Heat 's first head coach in the 1988-89 season and lasted three years with the expansion franchise , finishing with a <UNK> record ."
    },
    "sample_287": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "1992-93 Detroit Pistons ,",
        "sentence": "His last full stint as an NBA head coach was with the 1992-93 Detroit Pistons , a team he guided to a 40-42 record , and he filled in for"
    },
    "sample_288": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "for Riley for",
        "sentence": "His last full stint as an NBA head coach was with the 1992-93 Detroit Pistons , a team he guided to a 40-42 record , and he filled in for"
    },
    "sample_289": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "said Rothstein ,",
        "sentence": "Listen , I have n't been in the first chair in an NBA game since 1993 , \" said Rothstein , who also coached the WNBA 's Miami Sol for"
    },
    "sample_290": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the WNBA 's",
        "sentence": "Listen , I have n't been in the first chair in an NBA game since 1993 , \" said Rothstein , who also coached the WNBA 's Miami Sol for"
    },
    "sample_291": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "'s Miami Sol for",
        "sentence": "Listen , I have n't been in the first chair in an NBA game since 1993 , \" said Rothstein , who also coached the WNBA 's Miami Sol for"
    },
    "sample_292": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the WNBA was",
        "sentence": "Coaching the WNBA was a totally different story ."
    },
    "sample_293": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Riley 's",
        "sentence": "Riley 's frustration has grown as the Heat have struggled this season , remaining mired below .500 ."
    },
    "sample_294": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Heat have",
        "sentence": "Riley 's frustration has grown as the Heat have struggled this season , remaining mired below .500 ."
    },
    "sample_295": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "forwards Antoine Walker and",
        "sentence": "Plus , on Wednesday he deactivated forwards Antoine Walker and James Posey because neither met a Jan. 1 deadline for a team conditioning goal regarding body fat ."
    },
    "sample_296": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and James Posey because",
        "sentence": "Plus , on Wednesday he deactivated forwards Antoine Walker and James Posey because neither met a Jan. 1 deadline for a team conditioning goal regarding body fat ."
    },
    "sample_297": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "\" Riley said",
        "sentence": "We 've had defensive lapses that are mind-boggling to me , \" Riley said . \""
    },
    "sample_298": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "when Shaq and",
        "sentence": "The offensive output will be corrected when Shaq and Dwyane and everybody 's healthy ."
    },
    "sample_299": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Dwyane and",
        "sentence": "The offensive output will be corrected when Shaq and Dwyane and everybody 's healthy ."
    },
    "sample_300": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "The Heat have",
        "sentence": "The Heat have n't had their preseason projected starting five together for any games yet this season because of all the injuries . \""
    },
    "sample_301": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "\" O'Neal said",
