{
    "sample_0": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Iran will",
        "sentence": "Iran will protest to the International Court of Justice at the Hague and other global bodies about the U.S.-funded Radio Free Europe , the Iran Daily reported Monday ."
    },
    "sample_1": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "at the Hague and",
        "sentence": "Iran will protest to the International Court of Justice at the Hague and other global bodies about the U.S.-funded Radio Free Europe , the Iran Daily reported Monday ."
    },
    "sample_2": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "U.S.-funded Radio Free Europe ,",
        "sentence": "Iran will protest to the International Court of Justice at the Hague and other global bodies about the U.S.-funded Radio Free Europe , the Iran Daily reported Monday ."
    },
    "sample_3": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "quoted Foreign Minister Kamal",
        "sentence": "It quoted Foreign Minister Kamal Kharrazi as saying the radio \" was set up to interfere in Iran 's internal affairs . \""
    },
    "sample_4": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "Minister Kamal Kharrazi as",
        "sentence": "It quoted Foreign Minister Kamal Kharrazi as saying the radio \" was set up to interfere in Iran 's internal affairs . \""
    },
    "sample_5": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the ICJ in",
        "sentence": "The English-language daily also did not say which organizations Iran will approach besides the ICJ in the Netherlands ."
    },
    "sample_6": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in the Netherlands .",
        "sentence": "The English-language daily also did not say which organizations Iran will approach besides the ICJ in the Netherlands ."
    },
    "sample_7": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "from Prague to",
        "sentence": "On Tuesday , Iran recalled its ambassador from Prague to protest the Czech government 's assistance to the radio and said it would reduce the level of its economic and"
    },
    "sample_8": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the Czech government",
        "sentence": "On Tuesday , Iran recalled its ambassador from Prague to protest the Czech government 's assistance to the radio and said it would reduce the level of its economic and"
    },
    "sample_9": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "to Iraq on",
        "sentence": "The American-sponsored station also began broadcasts directed to Iraq on Friday ."
    },
    "sample_10": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "The Farsi -",
        "sentence": "The Farsi - language service to Iran was approved by the Czech government in August ."
    },
    "sample_11": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "from Munich , Germany ,",
        "sentence": "Radio Free Europe began transmitting from Munich , Germany , in 1951 , spreading uncensored news to Soviet - controlled countries behind the Iron Curtain during the Cold War between"
    },
    "sample_12": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "to Soviet -",
        "sentence": "Radio Free Europe began transmitting from Munich , Germany , in 1951 , spreading uncensored news to Soviet - controlled countries behind the Iron Curtain during the Cold War between"
    },
    "sample_13": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Iron Curtain during",
        "sentence": "Radio Free Europe began transmitting from Munich , Germany , in 1951 , spreading uncensored news to Soviet - controlled countries behind the Iron Curtain during the Cold War between"
    },
    "sample_14": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the Cold War between",
        "sentence": "Radio Free Europe began transmitting from Munich , Germany , in 1951 , spreading uncensored news to Soviet - controlled countries behind the Iron Curtain during the Cold War between"
    },
    "sample_15": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the Communist East",
        "sentence": "Radio Free Europe began transmitting from Munich , Germany , in 1951 , spreading uncensored news to Soviet - controlled countries behind the Iron Curtain during the Cold War between"
    },
    "sample_16": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Nicaragua (",
        "sentence": "MANAGUA , Nicaragua ( AP ) -- Rodolfo Garcia , an Associated Press reporter who helped chronicle Nicaragua 's emergence out of civil war , a papal visit , volcanoes"
    },
    "sample_17": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "of civil war ,",
        "sentence": "MANAGUA , Nicaragua ( AP ) -- Rodolfo Garcia , an Associated Press reporter who helped chronicle Nicaragua 's emergence out of civil war , a papal visit , volcanoes"
    },
    "sample_18": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Managua after",
        "sentence": "MANAGUA , Nicaragua ( AP ) -- Rodolfo Garcia , an Associated Press reporter who helped chronicle Nicaragua 's emergence out of civil war , a papal visit , volcanoes"
    },
    "sample_19": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "for Radio Nicaragua ,",
        "sentence": "Garcia joined The Associated Press office in Managua in 1986 after working for Radio Nicaragua , where he was director of short-wave broadcasts , and after helping found a local"
    },
    "sample_20": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "of short-wave broadcasts",
        "sentence": "Garcia joined The Associated Press office in Managua in 1986 after working for Radio Nicaragua , where he was director of short-wave broadcasts , and after helping found a local"
    },
    "sample_21": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Sandinista government",
        "sentence": "For the AP , he covered the war between the Sandinista government and Contra rebels , the Sandinistas ' loss of power at the ballot box and the country 's"
    },
    "sample_22": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Contra rebels",
        "sentence": "For the AP , he covered the war between the Sandinista government and Contra rebels , the Sandinistas ' loss of power at the ballot box and the country 's"
    },
    "sample_23": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "on volcanic eruptions ,",
        "sentence": "He also reported on volcanic eruptions , the 1996 visit of Pope John Paul II and the ravages of Hurricane Mitch in 1998 . \""
    },
    "sample_24": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of Pope John Paul II and",
        "sentence": "He also reported on volcanic eruptions , the 1996 visit of Pope John Paul II and the ravages of Hurricane Mitch in 1998 . \""
    },
    "sample_25": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of Hurricane Mitch in",
        "sentence": "He also reported on volcanic eruptions , the 1996 visit of Pope John Paul II and the ravages of Hurricane Mitch in 1998 . \""
    },
    "sample_26": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "for Mexico and",
        "sentence": "He worked under very difficult conditions created by a civil war but always managed to maintain total objectivity and a fair vision under pressure in reporting for The Associated Press"
    },
    "sample_27": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Central America .",
        "sentence": "He worked under very difficult conditions created by a civil war but always managed to maintain total objectivity and a fair vision under pressure in reporting for The Associated Press"
    },
    "sample_28": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the National Autonomous University of Nicaragua .",
        "sentence": "He attended the National Autonomous University of Nicaragua ."
    },
    "sample_29": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "including diabetes and",
        "sentence": "Garcia suffered a series of illnesses last year , including diabetes and cancer ."
    },
    "sample_30": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "and cancer .",
        "sentence": "Garcia suffered a series of illnesses last year , including diabetes and cancer ."
    },
    "sample_31": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of India 's",
        "sentence": "Nikhil Chakravarty , one of India 's best known journalist s , has died ."
    },
    "sample_32": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "known journalist s",
        "sentence": "Nikhil Chakravarty , one of India 's best known journalist s , has died ."
    },
    "sample_33": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "from brain cancer and",
        "sentence": "Chakravarty was suffering from brain cancer and died in hospital on Saturday , his family said ."
    },
    "sample_34": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Politics was",
        "sentence": "Politics was his forte and his columns appeared in leading Indian newspapers and magazines ."
    },
    "sample_35": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "leading Indian newspapers and",
        "sentence": "Politics was his forte and his columns appeared in leading Indian newspapers and magazines ."
    },
    "sample_36": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of Prasar Bharati ,",
        "sentence": "Last year , the government appointed him chief of Prasar Bharati , an autonomous corporation set up to end government control of radio and television ."
    },
    "sample_37": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "autonomous corporation set",
        "sentence": "Last year , the government appointed him chief of Prasar Bharati , an autonomous corporation set up to end government control of radio and television ."
    },
    "sample_38": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "from Calcutta University and",
        "sentence": "He graduated from Calcutta University and studied at Oxford University 's Merton College in England ."
    },
    "sample_39": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "at Oxford University 's Merton College in",
        "sentence": "He graduated from Calcutta University and studied at Oxford University 's Merton College in England ."
    },
    "sample_40": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "to journalism as",
        "sentence": "Chakravarty taught history at Calcutta University in the 1930s before taking to journalism as correspondent of a weekly brought out by the Communist Party of India ."
    },
    "sample_41": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Communist Party of India .",
        "sentence": "Chakravarty taught history at Calcutta University in the 1930s before taking to journalism as correspondent of a weekly brought out by the Communist Party of India ."
    },
    "sample_42": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "Minister Indira Gandhi imposed",
        "sentence": "He closed the Mainstream weekly for a while when Prime Minister Indira Gandhi imposed emergency rule in India 1975-77 , jailing political opponents and imposing censorship on newspapers and magazines"
    },
    "sample_43": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "captain Courtney Walsh ,",
        "sentence": "Word of the agreement leaked out when former captain Courtney Walsh , head of the West Indies players association , told the Caribbean News Agency that Lara and Hooper had"
    },
    "sample_44": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the West Indies players",
        "sentence": "Word of the agreement leaked out when former captain Courtney Walsh , head of the West Indies players association , told the Caribbean News Agency that Lara and Hooper had"
    },
    "sample_45": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Caribbean News Agency that",
        "sentence": "Word of the agreement leaked out when former captain Courtney Walsh , head of the West Indies players association , told the Caribbean News Agency that Lara and Hooper had"
    },
    "sample_46": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "that Lara and",
        "sentence": "Word of the agreement leaked out when former captain Courtney Walsh , head of the West Indies players association , told the Caribbean News Agency that Lara and Hooper had"
    },
    "sample_47": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Hooper had",
        "sentence": "Word of the agreement leaked out when former captain Courtney Walsh , head of the West Indies players association , told the Caribbean News Agency that Lara and Hooper had"
    },
    "sample_48": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the West Indies Cricket Board fired",
        "sentence": "The crisis came to a head last Wednesday when the West Indies Cricket Board fired superstar batsman Lara as captain and Hooper as vice-captain ."
    },
    "sample_49": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "superstar batsman Lara",
        "sentence": "The crisis came to a head last Wednesday when the West Indies Cricket Board fired superstar batsman Lara as captain and Hooper as vice-captain ."
    },
    "sample_50": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", treasurer of",
        "sentence": "Jimmy Adams , treasurer of the players ' assocation , negotiated on behalf of the players Monday with Rousseau ."
    },
    "sample_51": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", negotiated on",
        "sentence": "Jimmy Adams , treasurer of the players ' assocation , negotiated on behalf of the players Monday with Rousseau ."
    },
    "sample_52": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Ali Bacher ,",
        "sentence": "Ali Bacher , head of South African cricket , also was directly involved in Monday 's talks after sitting on the sidelines Sunday ."
    },
    "sample_53": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of South African cricket ,",
        "sentence": "Ali Bacher , head of South African cricket , also was directly involved in Monday 's talks after sitting on the sidelines Sunday ."
    },
    "sample_54": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "manager Clive Lloyd and",
        "sentence": "West Indies tour manager Clive Lloyd and WICB member Joel Garner were also involved in the talks which began Friday ."
    },
    "sample_55": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "member Joel Garner were",
        "sentence": "West Indies tour manager Clive Lloyd and WICB member Joel Garner were also involved in the talks which began Friday ."
    },
    "sample_56": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "a sponsorship deal",
        "sentence": "Progress was reported over the weekend with the announcement of a sponsorship deal offered by former South African wicketkeeper David Richardson , who runs a sports marketing firm in Johannesburg"
    },
    "sample_57": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "African wicketkeeper David",
        "sentence": "Progress was reported over the weekend with the announcement of a sponsorship deal offered by former South African wicketkeeper David Richardson , who runs a sports marketing firm in Johannesburg"
    },
    "sample_58": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "wicketkeeper David Richardson ,",
        "sentence": "Progress was reported over the weekend with the announcement of a sponsorship deal offered by former South African wicketkeeper David Richardson , who runs a sports marketing firm in Johannesburg"
    },
    "sample_59": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "sports marketing firm",
        "sentence": "Progress was reported over the weekend with the announcement of a sponsorship deal offered by former South African wicketkeeper David Richardson , who runs a sports marketing firm in Johannesburg"
    },
    "sample_60": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Johannesburg .",
        "sentence": "Progress was reported over the weekend with the announcement of a sponsorship deal offered by former South African wicketkeeper David Richardson , who runs a sports marketing firm in Johannesburg"
    },
    "sample_61": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Thailand at",
        "sentence": "Paintings and other art objects once displayed in elegant offices were snapped up this weekend in Thailand at an auction of assets of collapsed financial firms , Thai media reported"
    },
    "sample_62": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "an auction of",
        "sentence": "Paintings and other art objects once displayed in elegant offices were snapped up this weekend in Thailand at an auction of assets of collapsed financial firms , Thai media reported"
    },
    "sample_63": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "collapsed financial firms ,",
        "sentence": "Paintings and other art objects once displayed in elegant offices were snapped up this weekend in Thailand at an auction of assets of collapsed financial firms , Thai media reported"
    },
    "sample_64": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "million baht (",
        "sentence": "The three-day auction of more than 1,000 items , which ended Sunday , was expected to bring in more than an initial estimate of 30 million baht ( dlrs 697,000"
    },
    "sample_65": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "to liquidate the",
        "sentence": "The paintings , sculptures and other art-related objects were seized by Thailand 's Financial Restructuring Authority , a government agency set up to liquidate the assets of 56 finance companies"
    },
    "sample_66": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the International Monetary Fund as",
        "sentence": "The closings were required by the International Monetary Fund as part of its dlrs 17.2 billion bailout program for the depressed Thai economy ."
    },
    "sample_67": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "depressed Thai economy .",
        "sentence": "The closings were required by the International Monetary Fund as part of its dlrs 17.2 billion bailout program for the depressed Thai economy ."
    },
    "sample_68": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Bangkok Post .",
        "sentence": "The going prices have been very high , much higher than I expected , \" an art gallery owner , <UNK> <UNK> , was quoted as saying by the Bangkok"
    },
    "sample_69": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "Minister Chuan Leekpai donated",
        "sentence": "Prime Minister Chuan Leekpai donated two of his sketches to the auction , which was handled by Christies , the British auction house ."
    },
    "sample_70": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "by Christies ,",
        "sentence": "Prime Minister Chuan Leekpai donated two of his sketches to the auction , which was handled by Christies , the British auction house ."
    },
    "sample_71": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "'s Queen Sirikit <UNK> Convention Center .",
        "sentence": "It was held at Bangkok 's Queen Sirikit <UNK> Convention Center ."
    },
    "sample_72": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "A prosecutor on",
        "sentence": "A prosecutor on Friday left open the possibility that former apartheid President P.W. Botha would be put on trial for abuses committed during white rule ."
    },
    "sample_73": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "President P.W. Botha would",
        "sentence": "A prosecutor on Friday left open the possibility that former apartheid President P.W. Botha would be put on trial for abuses committed during white rule ."
    },
    "sample_74": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "during white rule .",
        "sentence": "A prosecutor on Friday left open the possibility that former apartheid President P.W. Botha would be put on trial for abuses committed during white rule ."
    },
    "sample_75": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Truth and Reconciliation Commission ( South Africa ) ,",
        "sentence": "Prosecutor Jan D'Oliveira said he currently has insufficient evidence to prosecute Botha , but that information collected by the Truth and Reconciliation Commission ( South Africa ) , which investigated"
    },
    "sample_76": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the African National Congress '",
        "sentence": "It said Botha had ordered the 1987 bombing of the African National Congress ' London headquarters and the 1988 bombing of a Johannesburg building housing an anti-apartheid group ."
    },
    "sample_77": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "a Johannesburg building",
        "sentence": "It said Botha had ordered the 1987 bombing of the African National Congress ' London headquarters and the 1988 bombing of a Johannesburg building housing an anti-apartheid group ."
    },
    "sample_78": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "grant amnesty to",
        "sentence": "The commission can grant amnesty to those who fully confess to politically motivated abuses committed during apartheid ."
    },
    "sample_79": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of contempt of court for",
        "sentence": "Earlier this year , Botha was convicted of contempt of court for refusing to testify before the commission ."
    },
    "sample_80": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "10,000 rand (",
        "sentence": "He was handed a suspended one-year jail sentence and a 10,000 rand ( dlrs 5,700 ) fine ."
    },
    "sample_81": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of Iran 's",
        "sentence": "The head of Iran 's prisoner of war commission met with two Iraqi Cabinet ministers Saturday in a bid to glean information about thousands of Iranian POWs allegedly in Iraq"
    },
    "sample_82": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "'s prisoner of war commission",
        "sentence": "The head of Iran 's prisoner of war commission met with two Iraqi Cabinet ministers Saturday in a bid to glean information about thousands of Iranian POWs allegedly in Iraq"
    },
    "sample_83": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "two Iraqi Cabinet ministers Saturday",
        "sentence": "The head of Iran 's prisoner of war commission met with two Iraqi Cabinet ministers Saturday in a bid to glean information about thousands of Iranian POWs allegedly in Iraq"
    },
    "sample_84": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "official Iraqi News Agency reported",
        "sentence": "The head of Iran 's prisoner of war commission met with two Iraqi Cabinet ministers Saturday in a bid to glean information about thousands of Iranian POWs allegedly in Iraq"
    },
    "sample_85": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "Minister Mohammed Saeed al-Sahhaf told",
        "sentence": "Iraqi Foreign Minister Mohammed Saeed al-Sahhaf told Abdullah <UNK> that the two states needed to \" speed up the closure of what remains from the POW and <UNK> file ,"
    },
    "sample_86": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and <UNK> file",
        "sentence": "Iraqi Foreign Minister Mohammed Saeed al-Sahhaf told Abdullah <UNK> that the two states needed to \" speed up the closure of what remains from the POW and <UNK> file ,"
    },
    "sample_87": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "1980-88 Iran-Iraq War .",
        "sentence": "Iraq has long maintained that it has released all Iranian prisoners captured in the 1980-88 Iran-Iraq War ."
    },
    "sample_88": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the International Committee of the Red Cross to",
        "sentence": "The countries accuse each other of hiding POWs and preventing visits by the International Committee of the Red Cross to prisoner camps ."
    },
    "sample_89": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Baghdad ,",
        "sentence": "The ICRC representative in Baghdad , Manuel Bessler , told The Associated Press that his organization has had difficulty visiting POWs on both sides on a regular basis ."
    },
    "sample_90": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "The Associated Press that",
        "sentence": "The ICRC representative in Baghdad , Manuel Bessler , told The Associated Press that his organization has had difficulty visiting POWs on both sides on a regular basis ."
    },
    "sample_91": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Beanie Babies and",
        "sentence": "NEW YORK ( AP ) -- Home shoppers can buy airline tickets , Beanie Babies and garden tools via computer ."
    },
    "sample_92": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "million Rembrandt painting",
        "sentence": "Why not a $ 9 million Rembrandt painting ?"
    },
    "sample_93": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Sotheby 's",
        "sentence": "Sotheby 's , the New York auction house , said Tuesday that it will spend $ 25 million to launch <UNK> , an Internet site where the public will be"
    },
    "sample_94": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the New York auction",
        "sentence": "Sotheby 's , the New York auction house , said Tuesday that it will spend $ 25 million to launch <UNK> , an Internet site where the public will be"
    },
    "sample_95": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "York auction house ,",
        "sentence": "Sotheby 's , the New York auction house , said Tuesday that it will spend $ 25 million to launch <UNK> , an Internet site where the public will be"
    },
    "sample_96": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "on antiques ,",
        "sentence": "Sotheby 's , the New York auction house , said Tuesday that it will spend $ 25 million to launch <UNK> , an Internet site where the public will be"
    },
    "sample_97": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", sports memorabilia and",
        "sentence": "Sotheby 's , the New York auction house , said Tuesday that it will spend $ 25 million to launch <UNK> , an Internet site where the public will be"
    },
    "sample_98": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "other collectibles .",
        "sentence": "Sotheby 's , the New York auction house , said Tuesday that it will spend $ 25 million to launch <UNK> , an Internet site where the public will be"
    },
    "sample_99": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "major online auction ,",
        "sentence": "Sotheby 's first major online auction , planned for July , will feature baseball memorabilia ."
    },
    "sample_100": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "feature baseball memorabilia",
        "sentence": "Sotheby 's first major online auction , planned for July , will feature baseball memorabilia ."
    },
    "sample_101": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "their charge card numbers",
        "sentence": "And bids will only be accepted from customers who have registered their charge card numbers in advance ."
    },
    "sample_102": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "at Christie 's",
        "sentence": "Officials at Christie 's , another leading New York auction house , said they were also considering an online auction site ."
    },
    "sample_103": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": ", German railway pledge",
        "sentence": "Lufthansa , German railway pledge closer cooperation"
    },
    "sample_104": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "from planes to",
        "sentence": "Seeking to shift some domestic travel from planes to trains , Germany 's flag carrier , Lufthansa , and the German railway signed a letter of intent Monday to work"
    },
    "sample_105": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "to trains ,",
        "sentence": "Seeking to shift some domestic travel from planes to trains , Germany 's flag carrier , Lufthansa , and the German railway signed a letter of intent Monday to work"
    },
    "sample_106": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Germany 's",
        "sentence": "Seeking to shift some domestic travel from planes to trains , Germany 's flag carrier , Lufthansa , and the German railway signed a letter of intent Monday to work"
    },
    "sample_107": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Lufthansa ,",
        "sentence": "Seeking to shift some domestic travel from planes to trains , Germany 's flag carrier , Lufthansa , and the German railway signed a letter of intent Monday to work"
    },
    "sample_108": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "'s main hub in",
        "sentence": "The goal is to make it easier to travel by train to Lufthansa 's main hub in Frankfurt , instead of flying there ."
    },
    "sample_109": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Frankfurt ,",
        "sentence": "The goal is to make it easier to travel by train to Lufthansa 's main hub in Frankfurt , instead of flying there ."
    },
    "sample_110": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Cologne ,",
        "sentence": "Starting in 2001 , Lufthansa boss Juergen Weber hopes to eliminate such short hops _ between Frankfurt and Cologne , for example _ thus freeing up takeoff and landing slots"
    },
    "sample_111": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and landing slots for",
        "sentence": "Starting in 2001 , Lufthansa boss Juergen Weber hopes to eliminate such short hops _ between Frankfurt and Cologne , for example _ thus freeing up takeoff and landing slots"
    },
    "sample_112": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "- Deutsche Bahn deal",
        "sentence": "As part of the Lufthansa - Deutsche Bahn deal , passengers could check their luggage through at the train station for the Lufthansa flight they will catch at Frankfurt ."
    },
    "sample_113": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Bonn ,",
        "sentence": "Starting in September , the service will be extended to five other cities : Duesseldorf , Cologne , Bonn , Wuerzburg and Nuremberg ."
    },
    "sample_114": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Wuerzburg and",
        "sentence": "Starting in September , the service will be extended to five other cities : Duesseldorf , Cologne , Bonn , Wuerzburg and Nuremberg ."
    },
    "sample_115": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "partners United and",
        "sentence": "Passengers flying on Lufthansa partners United and SAS would also be able to use the service , he said ."
    },
    "sample_116": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and SAS would",
        "sentence": "Passengers flying on Lufthansa partners United and SAS would also be able to use the service , he said ."
    },
    "sample_117": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "about U.S. -",
        "sentence": "Iran to complain about U.S. - radio at the Hague tribunal"
    },
    "sample_118": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Iran will",
        "sentence": "Iran will protest to the International Court of Justice at the Hague and other global bodies about the U.S.-funded Radio Free Europe , the Iran Daily reported Monday ."
    },
    "sample_119": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "at the Hague and",
        "sentence": "Iran will protest to the International Court of Justice at the Hague and other global bodies about the U.S.-funded Radio Free Europe , the Iran Daily reported Monday ."
    },
    "sample_120": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "U.S.-funded Radio Free Europe ,",
        "sentence": "Iran will protest to the International Court of Justice at the Hague and other global bodies about the U.S.-funded Radio Free Europe , the Iran Daily reported Monday ."
    },
    "sample_121": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "Minister Kamal Kharrazi as",
        "sentence": "It quoted Foreign Minister Kamal Kharrazi as saying the radio \" was set up to interfere in Iran 's internal affairs . \""
    },
    "sample_122": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the ICJ in",
        "sentence": "The English-language daily also did not say which organizations Iran will approach besides the ICJ in the Netherlands ."
    },
    "sample_123": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in the Netherlands .",
        "sentence": "The English-language daily also did not say which organizations Iran will approach besides the ICJ in the Netherlands ."
    },
    "sample_124": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "from Prague to",
        "sentence": "On Tuesday , Iran recalled its ambassador from Prague to protest the Czech government 's assistance to the radio and said it would reduce the level of its economic and"
    },
    "sample_125": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the Czech government",
        "sentence": "On Tuesday , Iran recalled its ambassador from Prague to protest the Czech government 's assistance to the radio and said it would reduce the level of its economic and"
    },
    "sample_126": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "to Iraq on",
        "sentence": "The American-sponsored station also began broadcasts directed to Iraq on Friday ."
    },
    "sample_127": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "The Farsi -",
        "sentence": "The Farsi - language service to Iran was approved by the Czech government in August ."
    },
    "sample_128": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the Czech government in",
        "sentence": "The Farsi - language service to Iran was approved by the Czech government in August ."
    },
    "sample_129": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "from Munich , Germany ,",
        "sentence": "Radio Free Europe began transmitting from Munich , Germany , in 1951 , spreading uncensored news to Soviet - controlled countries behind the Iron Curtain during the Cold War between"
    },
    "sample_130": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "to Soviet -",
        "sentence": "Radio Free Europe began transmitting from Munich , Germany , in 1951 , spreading uncensored news to Soviet - controlled countries behind the Iron Curtain during the Cold War between"
    },
    "sample_131": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Iron Curtain during",
        "sentence": "Radio Free Europe began transmitting from Munich , Germany , in 1951 , spreading uncensored news to Soviet - controlled countries behind the Iron Curtain during the Cold War between"
    },
    "sample_132": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the Cold War between",
        "sentence": "Radio Free Europe began transmitting from Munich , Germany , in 1951 , spreading uncensored news to Soviet - controlled countries behind the Iron Curtain during the Cold War between"
    },
    "sample_133": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the Communist East",
        "sentence": "Radio Free Europe began transmitting from Munich , Germany , in 1951 , spreading uncensored news to Soviet - controlled countries behind the Iron Curtain during the Cold War between"
    },
    "sample_134": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "-- First Union Corp.",
        "sentence": "CHARLOTTE ( AP ) -- First Union Corp. says it has fired seven employees within the last week for sending pornographic and other inappropriate e-mail ."
    },
    "sample_135": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "sending pornographic and",
        "sentence": "CHARLOTTE ( AP ) -- First Union Corp. says it has fired seven employees within the last week for sending pornographic and other inappropriate e-mail ."
    },
    "sample_136": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "inappropriate e-mail .",
        "sentence": "CHARLOTTE ( AP ) -- First Union Corp. says it has fired seven employees within the last week for sending pornographic and other inappropriate e-mail ."
    },
    "sample_137": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "or hostile environment ,",
        "sentence": "The bank \" will not tolerate conduct that interferes with another person 's work performance or creates an intimidating , offensive or hostile environment , \" Deem said ."
    },
    "sample_138": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> The Charlotte Observer reported",
        "sentence": "The Charlotte Observer reported Friday that employees at the University Research Park office circulated e-mail that included videos of people having sex and other material of a sexual nature ."
    },
    "sample_139": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "a server .",
        "sentence": "The company stumbled on the e-mail when the volume of messages became so heavy it slowed down a server ."
    },
    "sample_140": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "'s home-equity division",
        "sentence": "One employee fired within the past week from the bank 's home-equity division was called into an office , shown a stack of e-mail and fired on the spot ,"
    },
    "sample_141": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "a Fortune 100 corporation",
        "sentence": "First Union , a Fortune 100 corporation , joins a number of companies taking swift and severe action for violations of company e-mail policy ."
    },
    "sample_142": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "from legal claims that",
        "sentence": "Companies are seeking to protect themselves from legal claims that their work environment is hostile ."
    },
    "sample_143": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "alleging sexual harassment have",
        "sentence": "An increasing number of lawsuits alleging sexual harassment have based claims in part on e-mails taken from company computer systems ."
    },
    "sample_144": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Syria opposes",
        "sentence": "Syria opposes attempts by the United States and Britain to overthrow Iraqi leader Saddam Hussein , Syrian Vice-President <UNK> Khaddam said Thursday ."
    },
    "sample_145": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the United States and",
        "sentence": "Syria opposes attempts by the United States and Britain to overthrow Iraqi leader Saddam Hussein , Syrian Vice-President <UNK> Khaddam said Thursday ."
    },
    "sample_146": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Britain to",
        "sentence": "Syria opposes attempts by the United States and Britain to overthrow Iraqi leader Saddam Hussein , Syrian Vice-President <UNK> Khaddam said Thursday ."
    },
    "sample_147": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "overthrow Iraqi leader",
        "sentence": "Syria opposes attempts by the United States and Britain to overthrow Iraqi leader Saddam Hussein , Syrian Vice-President <UNK> Khaddam said Thursday ."
    },
    "sample_148": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "leader Saddam Hussein ,",
        "sentence": "Syria opposes attempts by the United States and Britain to overthrow Iraqi leader Saddam Hussein , Syrian Vice-President <UNK> Khaddam said Thursday ."
    },
    "sample_149": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "Vice-President <UNK> Khaddam said",
        "sentence": "Syria opposes attempts by the United States and Britain to overthrow Iraqi leader Saddam Hussein , Syrian Vice-President <UNK> Khaddam said Thursday ."
    },
    "sample_150": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "serve Israel 's",
        "sentence": "Such moves would \" serve Israel 's design to disintegrate the Arab and Islamic world , \" Khaddam said after receiving his Iranian counterpart , Hassan Habibi , at Damascus"
    },
    "sample_151": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the Arab and",
        "sentence": "Such moves would \" serve Israel 's design to disintegrate the Arab and Islamic world , \" Khaddam said after receiving his Iranian counterpart , Hassan Habibi , at Damascus"
    },
    "sample_152": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "and Islamic world",
        "sentence": "Such moves would \" serve Israel 's design to disintegrate the Arab and Islamic world , \" Khaddam said after receiving his Iranian counterpart , Hassan Habibi , at Damascus"
    },
    "sample_153": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Hassan Habibi ,",
        "sentence": "Such moves would \" serve Israel 's design to disintegrate the Arab and Islamic world , \" Khaddam said after receiving his Iranian counterpart , Hassan Habibi , at Damascus"
    },
    "sample_154": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "at Damascus airport .",
        "sentence": "Such moves would \" serve Israel 's design to disintegrate the Arab and Islamic world , \" Khaddam said after receiving his Iranian counterpart , Hassan Habibi , at Damascus"
    },
    "sample_155": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in London last",
        "sentence": "British and American officials hosted meetings in London last month of 16 Iraqi dissident groups in a bid to promote cooperation among them . \""
    },
    "sample_156": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "and Palestinian questions",
        "sentence": "Habibi said the Iraqi and Palestinian questions were of great concern to Iran and Syria : \" There should be coordination between the two countries over these issues . \""
    },
    "sample_157": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "by Iranian Foreign Minister Kamal Kharrazi ,",
        "sentence": "Habibi , who is accompanied by Iranian Foreign Minister Kamal Kharrazi , is expected to meet Syrian President Hafez Assad during his three-day visit ."
    },
    "sample_158": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "President Hafez Assad during",
        "sentence": "Habibi , who is accompanied by Iranian Foreign Minister Kamal Kharrazi , is expected to meet Syrian President Hafez Assad during his three-day visit ."
    },
    "sample_159": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "1980-88 Iran-Iraq war .",
        "sentence": "Syria is Iran 's closest Arab ally and supported the Persian state during the 1980-88 Iran-Iraq war ."
    },
    "sample_160": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Gulf `",
        "sentence": "Cohen : Missile defense system in Gulf ` imperative '"
    },
    "sample_161": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "Secretary William Cohen said",
        "sentence": "U.S. Defense Secretary William Cohen said Saturday it has become \" imperative \" for U.S. allies in the Gulf to acquire a ballistic missile defense system to counter long range"
    },
    "sample_162": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "for U.S. allies",
        "sentence": "U.S. Defense Secretary William Cohen said Saturday it has become \" imperative \" for U.S. allies in the Gulf to acquire a ballistic missile defense system to counter long range"
    },
    "sample_163": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "a ballistic missile defense system to",
        "sentence": "U.S. Defense Secretary William Cohen said Saturday it has become \" imperative \" for U.S. allies in the Gulf to acquire a ballistic missile defense system to counter long range"
    },
    "sample_164": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "as Iran and",
        "sentence": "U.S. Defense Secretary William Cohen said Saturday it has become \" imperative \" for U.S. allies in the Gulf to acquire a ballistic missile defense system to counter long range"
    },
    "sample_165": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Iraq .",
        "sentence": "U.S. Defense Secretary William Cohen said Saturday it has become \" imperative \" for U.S. allies in the Gulf to acquire a ballistic missile defense system to counter long range"
    },
    "sample_166": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "with Bahrain and",
        "sentence": "Cohen said the United States has five defense systems under research and development and \" we hope we hope we can share that technology with Bahrain and other Gulf countries"
    },
    "sample_167": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "for Qatar ,",
        "sentence": "He was speaking to reporters before leaving for Qatar , his second stop in a six-nation Gulf tour , which includes the United Arab Emirates , Oman , Kuwait and"
    },
    "sample_168": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the United Arab Emirates ,",
        "sentence": "He was speaking to reporters before leaving for Qatar , his second stop in a six-nation Gulf tour , which includes the United Arab Emirates , Oman , Kuwait and"
    },
    "sample_169": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Oman ,",
        "sentence": "He was speaking to reporters before leaving for Qatar , his second stop in a six-nation Gulf tour , which includes the United Arab Emirates , Oman , Kuwait and"
    },
    "sample_170": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Saudi Arabia .",
        "sentence": "He was speaking to reporters before leaving for Qatar , his second stop in a six-nation Gulf tour , which includes the United Arab Emirates , Oman , Kuwait and"
    },
    "sample_171": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "under U.N. sanctions",
        "sentence": "Cohen said Iraq , under U.N. sanctions , continues efforts to acquire missile technology that has a longer than permissible range ."
    },
    "sample_172": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "U.N. sanctions ,",
        "sentence": "Cohen said Iraq , under U.N. sanctions , continues efforts to acquire missile technology that has a longer than permissible range ."
    },
    "sample_173": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "stymie illegal art traffic king",
        "sentence": "International police seek to stymie illegal art traffic king"
    },
    "sample_174": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Budapest to",
        "sentence": "Police officers from 23 countries met in Budapest to seek more efficient ways to combat illegal traffic in art treasures , a police official said Thursday ."
    },
    "sample_175": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "combat illegal traffic in",
        "sentence": "Police officers from 23 countries met in Budapest to seek more efficient ways to combat illegal traffic in art treasures , a police official said Thursday ."
    },
    "sample_176": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of Interpol ,",
        "sentence": "Held under the auspices of Interpol , the International Police Organization , the three-day closed meeting allowed the officers to make personal contact and to help their East European counterparts"
    },
    "sample_177": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the International Police Organization",
        "sentence": "Held under the auspices of Interpol , the International Police Organization , the three-day closed meeting allowed the officers to make personal contact and to help their East European counterparts"
    },
    "sample_178": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "their East European counterparts",
        "sentence": "Held under the auspices of Interpol , the International Police Organization , the three-day closed meeting allowed the officers to make personal contact and to help their East European counterparts"
    },
    "sample_179": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "while France has",
        "sentence": "We have a five-member team working on illegal art traffic , and the group was set up only this April , while France has over 30 policemen in the same"
    },
    "sample_180": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "\" Hungarian police",
        "sentence": "We have a five-member team working on illegal art traffic , and the group was set up only this April , while France has over 30 policemen in the same"
    },
    "sample_181": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "after communism collapsed",
        "sentence": "In 1990 , the year after communism collapsed , there were 702 registered cases in Hungary , and the total value of the stolen treasures was 71 million forints ("
    },
    "sample_182": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "million forints (",
        "sentence": "In 1990 , the year after communism collapsed , there were 702 registered cases in Hungary , and the total value of the stolen treasures was 71 million forints ("
    },
    "sample_183": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "a data base and",
        "sentence": "Work is underway in cataloging the country 's art treasures , establishing a data base and a network of contacts among art dealers , auctioneers and museums ."
    },
    "sample_184": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "a network of",
        "sentence": "Work is underway in cataloging the country 's art treasures , establishing a data base and a network of contacts among art dealers , auctioneers and museums ."
    },
    "sample_185": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "among art dealers ,",
        "sentence": "Work is underway in cataloging the country 's art treasures , establishing a data base and a network of contacts among art dealers , auctioneers and museums ."
    },
    "sample_186": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", auctioneers and",
        "sentence": "Work is underway in cataloging the country 's art treasures , establishing a data base and a network of contacts among art dealers , auctioneers and museums ."
    },
    "sample_187": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": Alan Shepard becomes",
        "sentence": "May 5 , 1961 : Alan Shepard becomes first American in space ."
    },
    "sample_188": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": John Glenn becomes",
        "sentence": "Feb. 20 , 1962 : John Glenn becomes first American in orbit ."
    },
    "sample_189": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in orbit .",
        "sentence": "Feb. 20 , 1962 : John Glenn becomes first American in orbit ."
    },
    "sample_190": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": Gus Grissom ,",
        "sentence": "Jan. 27 , 1967 : Gus Grissom , Edward White II and Roger Chaffee die in Apollo 1 spacecraft fire on launch pad ."
    },
    "sample_191": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Edward White II",
        "sentence": "Jan. 27 , 1967 : Gus Grissom , Edward White II and Roger Chaffee die in Apollo 1 spacecraft fire on launch pad ."
    },
    "sample_192": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Roger Chaffee die",
        "sentence": "Jan. 27 , 1967 : Gus Grissom , Edward White II and Roger Chaffee die in Apollo 1 spacecraft fire on launch pad ."
    },
    "sample_193": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Apollo 1 spacecraft",
        "sentence": "Jan. 27 , 1967 : Gus Grissom , Edward White II and Roger Chaffee die in Apollo 1 spacecraft fire on launch pad ."
    },
    "sample_194": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "1 spacecraft fire",
        "sentence": "Jan. 27 , 1967 : Gus Grissom , Edward White II and Roger Chaffee die in Apollo 1 spacecraft fire on launch pad ."
    },
    "sample_195": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "on launch pad .",
        "sentence": "Jan. 27 , 1967 : Gus Grissom , Edward White II and Roger Chaffee die in Apollo 1 spacecraft fire on launch pad ."
    },
    "sample_196": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": Apollo 11 's",
        "sentence": "July 20 , 1969 : Apollo 11 's Neil Armstrong and Buzz Aldrin land on moon ."
    },
    "sample_197": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "'s Neil Armstrong and",
        "sentence": "July 20 , 1969 : Apollo 11 's Neil Armstrong and Buzz Aldrin land on moon ."
    },
    "sample_198": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Buzz Aldrin land",
        "sentence": "July 20 , 1969 : Apollo 11 's Neil Armstrong and Buzz Aldrin land on moon ."
    },
    "sample_199": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "on moon .",
        "sentence": "July 20 , 1969 : Apollo 11 's Neil Armstrong and Buzz Aldrin land on moon ."
    },
    "sample_200": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "Soviet Soyuz spacecraft link",
        "sentence": "July 17 , 1975 : American Apollo and Soviet Soyuz spacecraft link in orbit ."
    },
    "sample_201": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": Columbia soars",
        "sentence": "April 12 , 1981 : Columbia soars on first space shuttle flight ."
    },
    "sample_202": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "first space shuttle flight",
        "sentence": "April 12 , 1981 : Columbia soars on first space shuttle flight ."
    },
    "sample_203": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": Sally Ride becomes",
        "sentence": "June 18 , 1983 : Sally Ride becomes first American woman in space ."
    },
    "sample_204": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": Challenger explodes",
        "sentence": "Jan. 28 , 1986 : Challenger explodes , killing all seven on board ."
    },
    "sample_205": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": Hubble Space Telescope is",
        "sentence": "April 25 , 1990 : Hubble Space Telescope is released into orbit ."
    },
    "sample_206": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": Norman Thagard is",
        "sentence": "March 14 , 1995 : Norman Thagard is first American to be launched on a Russian rocket ."
    },
    "sample_207": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "Russian rocket .",
        "sentence": "March 14 , 1995 : Norman Thagard is first American to be launched on a Russian rocket ."
    },
    "sample_208": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "visit Mir .",
        "sentence": "Two days later , he becomes first American to visit Mir ."
    },
    "sample_209": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": Atlantis docks",
        "sentence": "June 29 , 1995 : Atlantis docks with Mir in first <UNK> hookup ."
    },
    "sample_210": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": Shannon Lucid returns",
        "sentence": "Sept. 26 , 1996 : Shannon Lucid returns to Earth after <UNK> Mir mission , a U.S. space endurance record and a world record for women ."
    },
    "sample_211": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": Story Musgrave ,",
        "sentence": "Nov. 19 , 1996 : Story Musgrave , at age 61 , becomes oldest man in space ."
    },
    "sample_212": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": Discovery is",
        "sentence": "Oct. 29 , 1998 : Discovery is scheduled to blast off , carrying 77-year-old John Glenn back into orbit and making him oldest man in space ."
    },
    "sample_213": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Iraq and",
        "sentence": "Iraq and Iran have signed a deal that Iraq says will resolve their longstanding dispute over prisoners of war ."
    },
    "sample_214": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Iran have",
        "sentence": "Iraq and Iran have signed a deal that Iraq says will resolve their longstanding dispute over prisoners of war ."
    },
    "sample_215": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "over prisoners of war .",
        "sentence": "Iraq and Iran have signed a deal that Iraq says will resolve their longstanding dispute over prisoners of war ."
    },
    "sample_216": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Baghdad between",
        "sentence": "The agreement was reached following a week of talks in Baghdad between senior Iraqi officials and a visiting Iranian delegation headed by Abdullah <UNK> , head of Iran 's POW"
    },
    "sample_217": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "Iranian delegation headed",
        "sentence": "The agreement was reached following a week of talks in Baghdad between senior Iraqi officials and a visiting Iranian delegation headed by Abdullah <UNK> , head of Iran 's POW"
    },
    "sample_218": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "official Iraqi News Agency reported",
        "sentence": "The agreement was reached following a week of talks in Baghdad between senior Iraqi officials and a visiting Iranian delegation headed by Abdullah <UNK> , head of Iran 's POW"
    },
    "sample_219": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "POWs Tehran claims",
        "sentence": "<UNK> arrived in Baghdad last week with a list of thousands of Iranian POWs Tehran claims are still held by Iraq ."
    },
    "sample_220": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "law detainees .",
        "sentence": "In April , Iran released 5,584 Iraqi POWs and Iraq freed three POWs and 316 Iranians it classified as civil law detainees ."
    },
    "sample_221": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "largest repatriation of",
        "sentence": "It was the largest repatriation of Iranian and Iraqi POWs since 1990 , said the International Committee of the Red Cross , which supervised the swap ."
    },
    "sample_222": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the International Committee of the Red Cross ,",
        "sentence": "It was the largest repatriation of Iranian and Iraqi POWs since 1990 , said the International Committee of the Red Cross , which supervised the swap ."
    },
    "sample_223": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "The Iran-Iraq war ,",
        "sentence": "The Iran-Iraq war , in which more than more than 1 million people were killed or wounded , ended in 1988 ."
    },
    "sample_224": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "The Norsk Hydro ASA concern",
        "sentence": "The Norsk Hydro ASA concern announced plans Friday to build a hydrogen - burning power plant that it says will produce electricity with virtually no <UNK> emissions ."
    },
    "sample_225": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "a hydrogen -",
        "sentence": "The Norsk Hydro ASA concern announced plans Friday to build a hydrogen - burning power plant that it says will produce electricity with virtually no <UNK> emissions ."
    },
    "sample_226": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "burning power plant that",
        "sentence": "The Norsk Hydro ASA concern announced plans Friday to build a hydrogen - burning power plant that it says will produce electricity with virtually no <UNK> emissions ."
    },
    "sample_227": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "produce electricity with",
        "sentence": "The Norsk Hydro ASA concern announced plans Friday to build a hydrogen - burning power plant that it says will produce electricity with virtually no <UNK> emissions ."
    },
    "sample_228": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> emissions .",
        "sentence": "The Norsk Hydro ASA concern announced plans Friday to build a hydrogen - burning power plant that it says will produce electricity with virtually no <UNK> emissions ."
    },
    "sample_229": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "51-percent state-owned company notified",
        "sentence": "The 51-percent state-owned company notified the Norwegian Water Resources and Energy Directorate of plans to build the plant , to be called <UNK> , pending approval by government agencies ."
    },
    "sample_230": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Norwegian Water Resources and Energy Directorate of",
        "sentence": "The 51-percent state-owned company notified the Norwegian Water Resources and Energy Directorate of plans to build the plant , to be called <UNK> , pending approval by government agencies ."
    },
    "sample_231": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "from natural gas .",
        "sentence": "The hydrogen for the plant would be extracted from natural gas ."
    },
    "sample_232": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "major petroleum producer",
        "sentence": "Norsk Hydro , a major petroleum producer , now says studies have shown the proposal to be economically viable ."
    },
    "sample_233": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "'s carbon dioxide emissions",
        "sentence": "It also said the plant 's carbon dioxide emissions would be 90 percent lower than plants using natural gas ."
    },
    "sample_234": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Norway is",
        "sentence": "Norway is the world 's second-largest oil exporter , and also produces vast amounts of natural gas from its offshore fields ."
    },
    "sample_235": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "from hydroelectric plants .",
        "sentence": "Virtually all of the country 's electricity now comes from hydroelectric plants ."
    },
    "sample_236": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", nitrogen and",
        "sentence": "Under the company 's plans , natural gas , air and water would be mixed to produce hydrogen , nitrogen and carbon dioxide ."
    },
    "sample_237": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of Oslo .",
        "sentence": "Norsk Hydro wants to build the plant at <UNK> , an island about 500 kilometers ( 300 miles ) west of Oslo ."
    },
    "sample_238": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "revamp strategy to",
        "sentence": "Interpol needs to revamp strategy to keep abreast of crime"
    },
    "sample_239": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Interpol must",
        "sentence": "Interpol must modernize if it wants to effectively fight increasingly sophisticated crime syndicates in the next century , the police organization 's president said Thursday ."
    },
    "sample_240": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "sophisticated crime syndicates in",
        "sentence": "Interpol must modernize if it wants to effectively fight increasingly sophisticated crime syndicates in the next century , the police organization 's president said Thursday ."
    },
    "sample_241": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "international organized crime ,",
        "sentence": "A failure to modernize Interpol could mean the organization \" risks being displaced against a backdrop of international organized crime , \" he said ."
    },
    "sample_242": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "discuss terrorism ,",
        "sentence": "The former Japanese police official said the assembly also will discuss terrorism , which he called one of the \" new forms of criminality , \" as well as the"
    },
    "sample_243": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the illegal drug trade and",
        "sentence": "The former Japanese police official said the assembly also will discuss terrorism , which he called one of the \" new forms of criminality , \" as well as the"
    },
    "sample_244": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "and money laundering .",
        "sentence": "The former Japanese police official said the assembly also will discuss terrorism , which he called one of the \" new forms of criminality , \" as well as the"
    },
    "sample_245": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "gather evidence for",
        "sentence": "With crime becoming increasingly sophisticated , Kanemoto said , it has become harder for police officials to gather evidence for prosecution ."
    },
    "sample_246": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "a strategic development plan aimed",
        "sentence": "The police officials are expected to discuss a strategic development plan aimed at making Interpol more proactive by re-examining the needs of the group 's <UNK> states , Kanemoto said"
    },
    "sample_247": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "by Bear <UNK>",
        "sentence": "Alaska Hiker Killed by Bear"
    },
    "sample_248": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> ANCHORAGE ,",
        "sentence": "ANCHORAGE , Alaska ( AP ) -- A man on a day hike in a rural area was killed when a bear bit his head , Alaska State Troopers said"
    },
    "sample_249": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Alaska (",
        "sentence": "ANCHORAGE , Alaska ( AP ) -- A man on a day hike in a rural area was killed when a bear bit his head , Alaska State Troopers said"
    },
    "sample_250": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Alaska State Troopers said",
        "sentence": "ANCHORAGE , Alaska ( AP ) -- A man on a day hike in a rural area was killed when a bear bit his head , Alaska State Troopers said"
    },
    "sample_251": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Kenai National Wildlife Refuge near",
        "sentence": "Kenneth Cates , 53 , was found Wednesday morning on a horse trail in a heavily wooded area of the Kenai National Wildlife Refuge near his hometown of Soldotna ."
    },
    "sample_252": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of Soldotna .",
        "sentence": "Kenneth Cates , 53 , was found Wednesday morning on a horse trail in a heavily wooded area of the Kenai National Wildlife Refuge near his hometown of Soldotna ."
    },
    "sample_253": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "caliber rifle and",
        "sentence": "Troopers said Cates ' .280 - caliber rifle and two spent shell casings were found near the body , along with traces of blood that suggest that Cates may have"
    },
    "sample_254": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "when <UNK> Luis Cortes ,",
        "sentence": "Cates ' death is the first fatal bear mauling in Alaska since Feb. 8 , 1998 , when <UNK> Luis Cortes , 40 , was killed while working on a"
    },
    "sample_255": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "a seismic crew",
        "sentence": "Cates ' death is the first fatal bear mauling in Alaska since Feb. 8 , 1998 , when <UNK> Luis Cortes , 40 , was killed while working on a"
    },
    "sample_256": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Swanson River oil",
        "sentence": "Cates ' death is the first fatal bear mauling in Alaska since Feb. 8 , 1998 , when <UNK> Luis Cortes , 40 , was killed while working on a"
    },
    "sample_257": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "River oil field near",
        "sentence": "Cates ' death is the first fatal bear mauling in Alaska since Feb. 8 , 1998 , when <UNK> Luis Cortes , 40 , was killed while working on a"
    },
    "sample_258": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "near Kenai .",
        "sentence": "Cates ' death is the first fatal bear mauling in Alaska since Feb. 8 , 1998 , when <UNK> Luis Cortes , 40 , was killed while working on a"
    },
    "sample_259": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "President Saddam Hussein said",
        "sentence": "President Saddam Hussein said Saturday the United States will reap nothing but a \" harvest ... full of thorns \" from its campaign against Iraq ."
    },
    "sample_260": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the United States will",
        "sentence": "President Saddam Hussein said Saturday the United States will reap nothing but a \" harvest ... full of thorns \" from its campaign against Iraq ."
    },
    "sample_261": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "against Iraq .",
        "sentence": "President Saddam Hussein said Saturday the United States will reap nothing but a \" harvest ... full of thorns \" from its campaign against Iraq ."
    },
    "sample_262": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "1980-88 Iran-Iraq war ,",
        "sentence": "Addressing the nation on television to mark the anniversary of the end of the 1980-88 Iran-Iraq war , Saddam also urged Iran to normalize relations with Iraq ."
    },
    "sample_263": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "with U.N. arms",
        "sentence": "Saddam did not refer to his decision Wednesday to freeze cooperation with U.N. arms inspectors , but he said the United States and its allies would be misled if they"
    },
    "sample_264": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "its allies would",
        "sentence": "Saddam did not refer to his decision Wednesday to freeze cooperation with U.N. arms inspectors , but he said the United States and its allies would be misled if they"
    },
    "sample_265": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the Iranian government under",
        "sentence": "This is exactly what the Iranian government under the late Ayatollah Ruhollah Khomeini thought it could do in the war , but it failed , Saddam said . \""
    },
    "sample_266": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "late Ayatollah Ruhollah Khomeini thought",
        "sentence": "This is exactly what the Iranian government under the late Ayatollah Ruhollah Khomeini thought it could do in the war , but it failed , Saddam said . \""
    },
    "sample_267": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "unfair embargo neglect",
        "sentence": "Those imposing aggression on Iraq ... and the unfair embargo neglect this fact today , \" Saddam said , referring to sweeping sanctions the United Nations imposed after Iraq 's"
    },
    "sample_268": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "sweeping sanctions the",
        "sentence": "Those imposing aggression on Iraq ... and the unfair embargo neglect this fact today , \" Saddam said , referring to sweeping sanctions the United Nations imposed after Iraq 's"
    },
    "sample_269": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of Kuwait .",
        "sentence": "Those imposing aggression on Iraq ... and the unfair embargo neglect this fact today , \" Saddam said , referring to sweeping sanctions the United Nations imposed after Iraq 's"
    },
    "sample_270": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "an artillery salute",
        "sentence": "He had decreed that Saturday be celebrated as a day of victory over Iran , and an artillery salute of 101 guns boomed over Baghdad in the early morning ."
    },
    "sample_271": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "over Baghdad in",
        "sentence": "He had decreed that Saturday be celebrated as a day of victory over Iran , and an artillery salute of 101 guns boomed over Baghdad in the early morning ."
    },
    "sample_272": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "played patriotic songs",
        "sentence": "National radio and television played patriotic songs for the occasion ."
    },
    "sample_273": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Iraq and",
        "sentence": "Iraq and Iran have signed a deal that Iraq says will resolve their longstanding dispute over prisoners of war ."
    },
    "sample_274": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Iran have",
        "sentence": "Iraq and Iran have signed a deal that Iraq says will resolve their longstanding dispute over prisoners of war ."
    },
    "sample_275": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "over prisoners of war .",
        "sentence": "Iraq and Iran have signed a deal that Iraq says will resolve their longstanding dispute over prisoners of war ."
    },
    "sample_276": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Baghdad between",
        "sentence": "The agreement was reached following a week of talks in Baghdad between senior Iraqi officials and a visiting Iranian delegation headed by Abdullah <UNK> , head of Iran 's POW"
    },
    "sample_277": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "official Iraqi News Agency reported",
        "sentence": "The agreement was reached following a week of talks in Baghdad between senior Iraqi officials and a visiting Iranian delegation headed by Abdullah <UNK> , head of Iran 's POW"
    },
    "sample_278": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "POWs Tehran claims",
        "sentence": "<UNK> arrived in Baghdad last week with a list of thousands of Iranian POWs Tehran claims are still held by Iraq ."
    },
    "sample_279": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "largest repatriation of",
        "sentence": "It was the largest repatriation of Iranian and Iraqi POWs since 1990 , said the International Committee of the Red Cross , which supervised the swap ."
    },
    "sample_280": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the International Committee of the Red Cross ,",
        "sentence": "It was the largest repatriation of Iranian and Iraqi POWs since 1990 , said the International Committee of the Red Cross , which supervised the swap ."
    },
    "sample_281": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "The Iran-Iraq war ,",
        "sentence": "The Iran-Iraq war , in which more than more than 1 million people were killed or wounded , ended in 1988 ."
    },
    "sample_282": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "Cult guru 's",
        "sentence": "Cult guru 's lawyers lash at prosecutors , court"
    },
    "sample_283": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "a cult guru",
        "sentence": "Attorneys for a cult guru accused of murder in the nerve gas attack on Tokyo subways denounced his trial Thursday as \" unfair \" because some of the prosecutors '"
    },
    "sample_284": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the nerve gas attack",
        "sentence": "Attorneys for a cult guru accused of murder in the nerve gas attack on Tokyo subways denounced his trial Thursday as \" unfair \" because some of the prosecutors '"
    },
    "sample_285": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "on Tokyo subways",
        "sentence": "Attorneys for a cult guru accused of murder in the nerve gas attack on Tokyo subways denounced his trial Thursday as \" unfair \" because some of the prosecutors '"
    },
    "sample_286": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Shoko Asahara ,",
        "sentence": "Shoko Asahara , the leader of the Aum Shinri Kyo cult , is on trial on 17 charges in the March 20 , 1995 sarin attack that killed 12 people"
    },
    "sample_287": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Aum Shinri Kyo cult",
        "sentence": "Shoko Asahara , the leader of the Aum Shinri Kyo cult , is on trial on 17 charges in the March 20 , 1995 sarin attack that killed 12 people"
    },
    "sample_288": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "1995 sarin attack that",
        "sentence": "Shoko Asahara , the leader of the Aum Shinri Kyo cult , is on trial on 17 charges in the March 20 , 1995 sarin attack that killed 12 people"
    },
    "sample_289": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the gassing as",
        "sentence": "Other cult leaders have also been charged in the gassing as well as in other slayings ."
    },
    "sample_290": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "chief defense lawyer",
        "sentence": "Osamu Watanabe , Asahara 's chief defense lawyer , said the trial should not be allowed to go on . \""
    },
    "sample_291": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Tokyo District Court .",
