{
    "sample_0": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", FET ,",
        "sentence": "Its transfer characteristics are exponential , not linear , be it tube , FET , or transistor ."
    },
    "sample_1": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "approaching DC )",
        "sentence": "In a similar fashion , at very low frequencies ( approaching DC ) the device becomes more nonlinear and its gain drops ."
    },
    "sample_2": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "at DC the",
        "sentence": "Obviously at DC the capacitor 's impedance is infinitely high , and at high frequencies the inductance is infinitely high ."
    },
    "sample_3": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "capacitors C10 and",
        "sentence": "In the case of the Dynaco <UNK> for example ( see attached schematic ) coupling capacitors C10 and C11 are 0.1 uF ."
    },
    "sample_4": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "and C11 are",
        "sentence": "In the case of the Dynaco <UNK> for example ( see attached schematic ) coupling capacitors C10 and C11 are 0.1 uF ."
    },
    "sample_5": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "to V2 directly",
        "sentence": "Refer to the audio channel schematic again , keeping in mind that the \" dashed \" section is our addition , the original has the input connected to V2 directly"
    },
    "sample_6": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the St -70",
        "sentence": "It is very strange to think that some people use the St -70 to drive tweeters when it does n't \" tweet \" at all-it does kind of \" squeak"
    },
    "sample_7": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", C10 and",
        "sentence": "As mentioned earlier , the interstage coupling capacitors , C10 and C11 are too small ."
    },
    "sample_8": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "and C11 are",
        "sentence": "As mentioned earlier , the interstage coupling capacitors , C10 and C11 are too small ."
    },
    "sample_9": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "make C10 and",
        "sentence": "Note that as long as the input is DC coupled , it is not possible to make C10 and C11 big enough , as even a very large capacitor will"
    },
    "sample_10": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "and C11 big",
        "sentence": "Note that as long as the input is DC coupled , it is not possible to make C10 and C11 big enough , as even a very large capacitor will"
    },
    "sample_11": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "to DC input",
        "sentence": "Note that as long as the input is DC coupled , it is not possible to make C10 and C11 big enough , as even a very large capacitor will"
    },
    "sample_12": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the St -70",
        "sentence": "To install the input bandwidth limited filter on the St -70 you will need 8 parts : ( 2 ) 10,000 resistors , ( 2 ) 470,000 resistors ( 5"
    },
    "sample_13": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "from Radio Shack are",
        "sentence": "To install the input bandwidth limited filter on the St -70 you will need 8 parts : ( 2 ) 10,000 resistors , ( 2 ) 470,000 resistors ( 5"
    },
    "sample_14": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Radio Shack will",
        "sentence": "Again , Radio Shack will have adequate parts and if you can match them on a precision capacitance meter it will be helpful ."
    },
    "sample_15": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "Again Radio Shack will",
        "sentence": "Again Radio Shack will have adequate parts ."
    },
    "sample_16": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the St -70",
        "sentence": "Further detail improvements can be made to the St -70 ."
    },
    "sample_17": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "old St -70",
        "sentence": "The bias supply capacitors in old St -70 amps should be replaced ."
    },
    "sample_18": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "( C3 and",
        "sentence": "We suggest that the two original 50 uF capacitors ( C3 and C4 , located on the 7 lug terminal strip under the chassis ) be replaced with new 100"
    },
    "sample_19": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "at Radio Shack )",
        "sentence": "We suggest that the two original 50 uF capacitors ( C3 and C4 , located on the 7 lug terminal strip under the chassis ) be replaced with new 100"
    },
    "sample_20": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "( Dl )",
        "sentence": "Because selenium rectifiers ( the small little finned block located in the bottom middle of the chassis ) become resistive with age , you may be able to increase the"
    },
    "sample_21": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "of Rl (",
        "sentence": "Because the negative voltage to the bias supply will now be higher than stock , it probably will also be necessary to change the value of Rl ( 10,000 2"
    },
    "sample_22": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "volts DC across",
        "sentence": "Because the negative voltage to the bias supply will now be higher than stock , it probably will also be necessary to change the value of Rl ( 10,000 2"
    },
    "sample_23": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "of P1 and",
        "sentence": "Because the negative voltage to the bias supply will now be higher than stock , it probably will also be necessary to change the value of Rl ( 10,000 2"
    },
    "sample_24": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "and P2 .",
        "sentence": "Because the negative voltage to the bias supply will now be higher than stock , it probably will also be necessary to change the value of Rl ( 10,000 2"
    },
    "sample_25": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the St -70",
        "sentence": "In the St -70 the noise characteristics , gain , power , and slew rate are dependent upon having high quality tubes in the unit ."
    },
    "sample_26": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "CALL US FIRST at",
        "sentence": "DO NOT ship your vacuum tube amplifier to us to fix if you screw it up unless you CALL US FIRST at 651 <UNK> ."
    },
    "sample_27": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "new Input/Output <UNK>",
        "sentence": "A new Input/Output"
    },
    "sample_28": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "quality Pomona 5-way",
        "sentence": "with gold plated input jacks and high quality Pomona 5-way binding"
    },
    "sample_29": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Fuse blowing",
        "sentence": "Fuse blowing can be caused by two problems ."
    },
    "sample_30": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "bad 6CA7 tube",
        "sentence": "A fuse that blows soft or after a few minutes of operation indicates a problem with the audio circuits - probably a bad 6CA7 tube ."
    },
    "sample_31": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "with AC line",
        "sentence": "Note that the bias setting will vary with AC line voltage so the value is n't an absolute ."
    },
    "sample_32": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "larger C10 and",
        "sentence": "The larger C10 and C11 effectively takes them out of circuit for AC signal purposes after the input filters have been installed ."
    },
    "sample_33": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "and C11 effectively",
        "sentence": "The larger C10 and C11 effectively takes them out of circuit for AC signal purposes after the input filters have been installed ."
    },
    "sample_34": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "for AC signal",
        "sentence": "The larger C10 and C11 effectively takes them out of circuit for AC signal purposes after the input filters have been installed ."
    },
    "sample_35": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "( C6 ,",
        "sentence": "Note : Input circuit ( C6 , R5 , C7 , and R6 ) is new and replaces the original direct coupled input circuit ."
    },
    "sample_36": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", C7 ,",
        "sentence": "Note : Input circuit ( C6 , R5 , C7 , and R6 ) is new and replaces the original direct coupled input circuit ."
    },
    "sample_37": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and R6 )",
        "sentence": "Note : Input circuit ( C6 , R5 , C7 , and R6 ) is new and replaces the original direct coupled input circuit ."
    },
    "sample_38": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "except R7 leads",
        "sentence": "All wiring is removed from the input jacks except R7 leads and then the new input circuit is installed ."
    },
    "sample_39": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> C3 ,",
        "sentence": "C3 , C4 , C10 , and C11 are revised values ."
    },
    "sample_40": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", C10 ,",
        "sentence": "C3 , C4 , C10 , and C11 are revised values ."
    },
    "sample_41": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "and C11 are",
        "sentence": "C3 , C4 , C10 , and C11 are revised values ."
    },
    "sample_42": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "( P1 &",
        "sentence": "Adjust bias ( P1 & P2 ) for 1.56 volts across R20 ."
    },
    "sample_43": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "& P2 )",
        "sentence": "Adjust bias ( P1 & P2 ) for 1.56 volts across R20 ."
    },
    "sample_44": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "<UNK> L1 can",
        "sentence": "L1 can be replaced with a 30 10 watt resistor to make amplifier operational if L1"
    },
    "sample_45": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "if L1 <UNK>",
        "sentence": "L1 can be replaced with a 30 10 watt resistor to make amplifier operational if L1"
    },
    "sample_46": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "( PP )",
        "sentence": "behavior of polypropylene ( PP ) are examined ."
    },
    "sample_47": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of PP .",
        "sentence": "quality of PP ."
    },
    "sample_48": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> DSC and",
        "sentence": "DSC and WAX analysis demonstrate that the crystalline structure"
    },
    "sample_49": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and WAX analysis",
        "sentence": "DSC and WAX analysis demonstrate that the crystalline structure"
    },
    "sample_50": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of PP is",
        "sentence": "of PP is changed and the content of the beta crystalline increases through"
    },
    "sample_51": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of PP <UNK>",
        "sentence": "as strong stress , shatter and vibration , which alter the growth of PP"
    },
    "sample_52": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Pendleton (",
        "sentence": "Pendleton ( 2 ) also described an ultrasonic process"
    },
    "sample_53": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "on HDPE melts",
        "sentence": "( 3 ) reported that imposition of ultrasound on HDPE melts containing a"
    },
    "sample_54": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of PP for",
        "sentence": "of PP for the case when ultrasound is employed at the die entrance ."
    },
    "sample_55": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> PP ,",
        "sentence": "PP , 2401 , with a melt index of"
    },
    "sample_56": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Beijing ,",
        "sentence": "obtained from Yanshan Petrochemical Co. , Beijing , China ."
    },
    "sample_57": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", China .",
        "sentence": "obtained from Yanshan Petrochemical Co. , Beijing , China ."
    },
    "sample_58": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", L/D =",
        "sentence": "setup consists of a single - screw extruder ( d = 20 mm , L/D = 25 ) , with"
    },
    "sample_59": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "an American CS",
        "sentence": "was measured on an American CS - 127 Melt Flow Index measuring device at"
    },
    "sample_60": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "American CS -",
        "sentence": "was measured on an American CS - 127 Melt Flow Index measuring device at"
    },
    "sample_61": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of PP .",
        "sentence": "extrusion of PP ."
    },
    "sample_62": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of PP is",
        "sentence": "decrease of apparent viscosity of PP is also a function of ultrasonic"
    },
    "sample_63": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "that MFR increases",
        "sentence": "demonstrate that MFR increases after application of ultrasound under the"
    },
    "sample_64": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", MFR changes",
        "sentence": "But with low - intensity ultrasound , MFR changes"
    },
    "sample_65": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "/ D ^",
        "sentence": "ratios D / D ^ sub 0 ^ decrease with increasing ultrasonic irradiation power ."
    },
    "sample_66": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of PP ,",
        "sentence": "the processing of PP , and this effect must be a result of structural changes"
    },
    "sample_67": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", PP is",
        "sentence": "At the same time , PP is well known for its different"
    },
    "sample_68": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "by DSC and",
        "sentence": "samples were analyzed by DSC and <UNK> ."
    },
    "sample_69": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and <UNK> .",
        "sentence": "samples were analyzed by DSC and <UNK> ."
    },
    "sample_70": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "from DSC thermograms",
        "sentence": "from DSC thermograms ."
    },
    "sample_71": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> T ^",
        "sentence": "T ^ sub c ^ is the crystallization temperature , T ^ sub"
    },
    "sample_72": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Si ,",
        "sentence": "Si , the tangent of alpha , is"
    },
    "sample_73": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "-- T ^",
        "sentence": "with the use of ultrasonic vibration , ( T ^ sub onset ^ -- T ^ sub c ^ ) , Si and"
    },
    "sample_74": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Si and",
        "sentence": "with the use of ultrasonic vibration , ( T ^ sub onset ^ -- T ^ sub c ^ ) , Si and"
    },
    "sample_75": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of PP crystal",
        "sentence": "as well as accelerating the growth of PP crystal , and the decreased rate"
    },
    "sample_76": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> PP with",
        "sentence": "PP with ultrasound causes a preference for the growth of the <UNK>"
    },
    "sample_77": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "that PP samples",
        "sentence": "diffraction patterns that PP samples with and without ultrasonic treatment"
    },
    "sample_78": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of PP decrease",
        "sentence": "of crystal planes of PP decrease and values of S increase with ultrasonic"
    },
    "sample_79": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of PP have",
        "sentence": "disordered structure , so that the lattices of PP have an increased order ."
    },
    "sample_80": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "of PP may",
        "sentence": "implies that the polymorphic transitions alpha - > beta of PP may exist"
    },
    "sample_81": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "of PP by",
        "sentence": "to extrusion can improve the processing of PP by raising the die temperature"
    },
    "sample_82": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "like PP during",
        "sentence": "like PP during extrusion ."
    },
    "sample_83": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "extruded PP .",
        "sentence": "of the crystallinity of extruded PP ."
    },
    "sample_84": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of PP ,",
        "sentence": "effect on the growth of different crystal forms of PP , which causes an"
    },
    "sample_85": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> SI <UNK>",
        "sentence": "SI <UNK> , EN Popova ,"
    },
    "sample_86": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", EN Popova",
        "sentence": "SI <UNK> , EN Popova ,"
    },
    "sample_87": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "I. Salina ,",
        "sentence": "and Z. I. Salina , Deposited Doc ."
    },
    "sample_88": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", CM along",
        "sentence": "Isayev , CM along ,"
    },
    "sample_89": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> AI Isayev",
        "sentence": "AI Isayev and J. Chen , Rubber"
    },
    "sample_90": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> AI Isayev",
        "sentence": "AI Isayev , S. P. <UNK> ,"
    },
    "sample_91": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Techno /",
        "sentence": "Rubber Chemistry and Techno / ogy , 70 , 120 ( 1997 ) ."
    },
    "sample_92": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Polymer ,",
        "sentence": "A. E. Tonelli , Polymer , 28 , 2227 ( 1987 ) ."
    },
    "sample_93": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and DR Beckett",
        "sentence": "and DR Beckett , <UNK> Chem. , 75 , 136 ( 1964 ) ."
    },
    "sample_94": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> AK Gupta",
        "sentence": "AK Gupta and VB"
    },
    "sample_95": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and VB <UNK>",
        "sentence": "AK Gupta and VB"
    },
    "sample_96": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "other Marching Bands and",
        "sentence": "I 'm not in high school anymore but I do like to follow and learn from around the country from other Marching Bands and their marching shows ?"
    },
    "sample_97": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "doing Robin Hood :",
        "sentence": "My old hs is doing Robin Hood : Prince of thieves , and their ballad is Training Montage from Highlander ."
    },
    "sample_98": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "from Highlander .",
        "sentence": "My old hs is doing Robin Hood : Prince of thieves , and their ballad is Training Montage from Highlander ."
    },
    "sample_99": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Angola is",
        "sentence": "Angola is performing ' through the golden door ' ."
    },
    "sample_100": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> S1 :",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_101": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", S2 :",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_102": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", S3 :",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_103": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", S5 :",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_104": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", S6 :",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_105": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", S7 :",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_106": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", S8 :",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_107": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", S10 :",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_108": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", S11 :",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_109": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", S12 :",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_110": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", S13 :",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_111": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "a New Mexico Native",
        "sentence": "My school is doing a New Mexico Native American theme where we bring in all our state symbols into our show and we use teepees about 12 feet tall as"
    },
    "sample_112": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "Mexico Native American theme",
        "sentence": "My school is doing a New Mexico Native American theme where we bring in all our state symbols into our show and we use teepees about 12 feet tall as"
    },
    "sample_113": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Symphony 2,3",
        "sentence": "1812 Overture , Symphony 2,3 , and 4 I believe ."
    },
    "sample_114": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "school Class C )",
        "sentence": "our band ( high school Class C ) swept the competition last saturday ."
    },
    "sample_115": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "from X-men ,",
        "sentence": "I 'm just an alum that techs with the battery from time to time , but their show is \" The Hero : The Battle of Good vs. Evil ,"
    },
    "sample_116": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Batman ,",
        "sentence": "I 'm just an alum that techs with the battery from time to time , but their show is \" The Hero : The Battle of Good vs. Evil ,"
    },
    "sample_117": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Superman ,",
        "sentence": "I 'm just an alum that techs with the battery from time to time , but their show is \" The Hero : The Battle of Good vs. Evil ,"
    },
    "sample_118": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> S1 :",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_119": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", S2 :",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_120": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", S3 :",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_121": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", S5 :",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_122": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", S6 :",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_123": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", S7 :",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_124": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", S8 :",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_125": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", S10 :",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_126": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", S11 :",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_127": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", S12 :",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_128": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", S13 <UNK>",
        "sentence": "S1 : 18 , S2 : 39 , S3 : 53 , S4 : 36 , S5 : 20 , S6 : 25 , S7 : 25 , S8 :"
    },
    "sample_129": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Franklin County ,",
        "sentence": "Real Estate Appraisers in Franklin County , Missouri"
    },
    "sample_130": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Missouri <UNK>",
        "sentence": "Real Estate Appraisers in Franklin County , Missouri"
    },
    "sample_131": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Fast ,",
        "sentence": "Fast , Fast , Fast ?"
    },
    "sample_132": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Fast ,",
        "sentence": "Fast , Fast , Fast ?"
    },
    "sample_133": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": ", Fast ?",
        "sentence": "Fast , Fast , Fast ?"
    },
    "sample_134": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Mastercard &",
        "sentence": "Mastercard & Visa - 5 years experience as a Loan Officer prior to becoming a CRA ."
    },
    "sample_135": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "& Visa -",
        "sentence": "Mastercard & Visa - 5 years experience as a Loan Officer prior to becoming a CRA ."
    },
    "sample_136": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "a CRA .",
        "sentence": "Mastercard & Visa - 5 years experience as a Loan Officer prior to becoming a CRA ."
    },
    "sample_137": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Franklin County ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Franklin County , Missouri : Beaufort , Berger , Catawissa , Gerald , Gray Summit , Grubville , Labadie , Leslie , Lonedell , Luebbering , New Haven"
    },
    "sample_138": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Missouri :",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Franklin County , Missouri : Beaufort , Berger , Catawissa , Gerald , Gray Summit , Grubville , Labadie , Leslie , Lonedell , Luebbering , New Haven"
    },
    "sample_139": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": Beaufort ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Franklin County , Missouri : Beaufort , Berger , Catawissa , Gerald , Gray Summit , Grubville , Labadie , Leslie , Lonedell , Luebbering , New Haven"
    },
    "sample_140": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Catawissa ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Franklin County , Missouri : Beaufort , Berger , Catawissa , Gerald , Gray Summit , Grubville , Labadie , Leslie , Lonedell , Luebbering , New Haven"
    },
    "sample_141": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Gray Summit ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Franklin County , Missouri : Beaufort , Berger , Catawissa , Gerald , Gray Summit , Grubville , Labadie , Leslie , Lonedell , Luebbering , New Haven"
    },
    "sample_142": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Labadie ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Franklin County , Missouri : Beaufort , Berger , Catawissa , Gerald , Gray Summit , Grubville , Labadie , Leslie , Lonedell , Luebbering , New Haven"
    },
    "sample_143": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Lonedell ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Franklin County , Missouri : Beaufort , Berger , Catawissa , Gerald , Gray Summit , Grubville , Labadie , Leslie , Lonedell , Luebbering , New Haven"
    },
    "sample_144": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Luebbering ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Franklin County , Missouri : Beaufort , Berger , Catawissa , Gerald , Gray Summit , Grubville , Labadie , Leslie , Lonedell , Luebbering , New Haven"
    },
    "sample_145": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", New Haven ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Franklin County , Missouri : Beaufort , Berger , Catawissa , Gerald , Gray Summit , Grubville , Labadie , Leslie , Lonedell , Luebbering , New Haven"
    },
    "sample_146": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Pacific ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Franklin County , Missouri : Beaufort , Berger , Catawissa , Gerald , Gray Summit , Grubville , Labadie , Leslie , Lonedell , Luebbering , New Haven"
    },
    "sample_147": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Robertsville ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Franklin County , Missouri : Beaufort , Berger , Catawissa , Gerald , Gray Summit , Grubville , Labadie , Leslie , Lonedell , Luebbering , New Haven"
    },
    "sample_148": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Saint Clair ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Franklin County , Missouri : Beaufort , Berger , Catawissa , Gerald , Gray Summit , Grubville , Labadie , Leslie , Lonedell , Luebbering , New Haven"
    },
    "sample_149": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Stanton ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Franklin County , Missouri : Beaufort , Berger , Catawissa , Gerald , Gray Summit , Grubville , Labadie , Leslie , Lonedell , Luebbering , New Haven"
    },
    "sample_150": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Sullivan ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Franklin County , Missouri : Beaufort , Berger , Catawissa , Gerald , Gray Summit , Grubville , Labadie , Leslie , Lonedell , Luebbering , New Haven"
    },
    "sample_151": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Union ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Franklin County , Missouri : Beaufort , Berger , Catawissa , Gerald , Gray Summit , Grubville , Labadie , Leslie , Lonedell , Luebbering , New Haven"
    },
    "sample_152": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Villa Ridge ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Franklin County , Missouri : Beaufort , Berger , Catawissa , Gerald , Gray Summit , Grubville , Labadie , Leslie , Lonedell , Luebbering , New Haven"
    },
    "sample_153": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Washington ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Franklin County , Missouri : Beaufort , Berger , Catawissa , Gerald , Gray Summit , Grubville , Labadie , Leslie , Lonedell , Luebbering , New Haven"
    },
    "sample_154": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Wildwood .",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Franklin County , Missouri : Beaufort , Berger , Catawissa , Gerald , Gray Summit , Grubville , Labadie , Leslie , Lonedell , Luebbering , New Haven"
    },
    "sample_155": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the Internet ,",
        "sentence": "On the Internet , Location Is n't Expensive , It 's Priceless"
    },
    "sample_156": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "'s Priceless <UNK>",
        "sentence": "On the Internet , Location Is n't Expensive , It 's Priceless"
    },
    "sample_157": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Real Estate Appraisers",
        "sentence": "Real Estate Appraisers in Washington County , New York"
    },
    "sample_158": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Washington County ,",
        "sentence": "Real Estate Appraisers in Washington County , New York"
    },
    "sample_159": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", New York <UNK>",
        "sentence": "Real Estate Appraisers in Washington County , New York"
    },
    "sample_160": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", FHA &",
        "sentence": "Our appraisers specialize in residential appraising , with an emphasis on Mortgages , FHA & Relocation appraisals ."
    },
    "sample_161": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of Albany ,",
        "sentence": "Residential Appraisal Services , covering the counties of Albany , Columbia , Greene , Rensselaer , Saratoga , Schenectady , Washington and Warren ."
    },
    "sample_162": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Columbia ,",
        "sentence": "Residential Appraisal Services , covering the counties of Albany , Columbia , Greene , Rensselaer , Saratoga , Schenectady , Washington and Warren ."
    },
    "sample_163": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Greene ,",
        "sentence": "Residential Appraisal Services , covering the counties of Albany , Columbia , Greene , Rensselaer , Saratoga , Schenectady , Washington and Warren ."
    },
    "sample_164": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Rensselaer ,",
        "sentence": "Residential Appraisal Services , covering the counties of Albany , Columbia , Greene , Rensselaer , Saratoga , Schenectady , Washington and Warren ."
    },
    "sample_165": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Saratoga ,",
        "sentence": "Residential Appraisal Services , covering the counties of Albany , Columbia , Greene , Rensselaer , Saratoga , Schenectady , Washington and Warren ."
    },
    "sample_166": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Schenectady ,",
        "sentence": "Residential Appraisal Services , covering the counties of Albany , Columbia , Greene , Rensselaer , Saratoga , Schenectady , Washington and Warren ."
    },
    "sample_167": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Washington and",
        "sentence": "Residential Appraisal Services , covering the counties of Albany , Columbia , Greene , Rensselaer , Saratoga , Schenectady , Washington and Warren ."
    },
    "sample_168": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "and Warren .",
        "sentence": "Residential Appraisal Services , covering the counties of Albany , Columbia , Greene , Rensselaer , Saratoga , Schenectady , Washington and Warren ."
    },
    "sample_169": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "by Cell Phone or",
        "sentence": "For Immediate Assistance contact us by Cell Phone or Email ."
    },
    "sample_170": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Washington County ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Washington County , New York : Argyle , Cambridge , Clemons , Comstock , Cossayuna , E Greenwich , East Greenwich , Fort Ann , Fort Edward ,"
    },
    "sample_171": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", New York :",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Washington County , New York : Argyle , Cambridge , Clemons , Comstock , Cossayuna , E Greenwich , East Greenwich , Fort Ann , Fort Edward ,"
    },
    "sample_172": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ": Argyle ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Washington County , New York : Argyle , Cambridge , Clemons , Comstock , Cossayuna , E Greenwich , East Greenwich , Fort Ann , Fort Edward ,"
    },
    "sample_173": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Cambridge ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Washington County , New York : Argyle , Cambridge , Clemons , Comstock , Cossayuna , E Greenwich , East Greenwich , Fort Ann , Fort Edward ,"
    },
    "sample_174": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", East Greenwich ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Washington County , New York : Argyle , Cambridge , Clemons , Comstock , Cossayuna , E Greenwich , East Greenwich , Fort Ann , Fort Edward ,"
    },
    "sample_175": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Fort Ann ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Washington County , New York : Argyle , Cambridge , Clemons , Comstock , Cossayuna , E Greenwich , East Greenwich , Fort Ann , Fort Edward ,"
    },
    "sample_176": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Fort Edward ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Washington County , New York : Argyle , Cambridge , Clemons , Comstock , Cossayuna , E Greenwich , East Greenwich , Fort Ann , Fort Edward ,"
    },
    "sample_177": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Greenwich ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Washington County , New York : Argyle , Cambridge , Clemons , Comstock , Cossayuna , E Greenwich , East Greenwich , Fort Ann , Fort Edward ,"
    },
    "sample_178": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Hampton ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Washington County , New York : Argyle , Cambridge , Clemons , Comstock , Cossayuna , E Greenwich , East Greenwich , Fort Ann , Fort Edward ,"
    },
    "sample_179": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Hartford ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Washington County , New York : Argyle , Cambridge , Clemons , Comstock , Cossayuna , E Greenwich , East Greenwich , Fort Ann , Fort Edward ,"
    },
    "sample_180": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Hudson Falls ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Washington County , New York : Argyle , Cambridge , Clemons , Comstock , Cossayuna , E Greenwich , East Greenwich , Fort Ann , Fort Edward ,"
    },
    "sample_181": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Salem ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Washington County , New York : Argyle , Cambridge , Clemons , Comstock , Cossayuna , E Greenwich , East Greenwich , Fort Ann , Fort Edward ,"
    },
    "sample_182": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Shushan ,",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Washington County , New York : Argyle , Cambridge , Clemons , Comstock , Cossayuna , E Greenwich , East Greenwich , Fort Ann , Fort Edward ,"
    },
    "sample_183": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Whitehall .",
        "sentence": "Cities/Towns in Washington County , New York : Argyle , Cambridge , Clemons , Comstock , Cossayuna , E Greenwich , East Greenwich , Fort Ann , Fort Edward ,"
    },
    "sample_184": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "the Internet <UNK>",
        "sentence": "On the Internet"
    },
    "sample_185": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Harvard Graduate School of Design .",
        "sentence": "Harvard Graduate School of Design ."
    },
    "sample_186": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Cambridge ,",
        "sentence": "Cambridge , MA , 1990 ."
    },
    "sample_187": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", MA ,",
        "sentence": "Cambridge , MA , 1990 ."
    },
    "sample_188": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Cambridge ,",
        "sentence": "Cambridge , MA , 1990 ."
    },
    "sample_189": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", MA ,",
        "sentence": "Cambridge , MA , 1990 ."
    },
    "sample_190": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Cambridge ,",
        "sentence": "Cambridge , MA , 2002 ."
    },
    "sample_191": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", MA ,",
        "sentence": "Cambridge , MA , 2002 ."
    },
    "sample_192": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Cambridge ,",
        "sentence": "Cambridge , MA , 2005 ."
    },
    "sample_193": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", MA ,",
        "sentence": "Cambridge , MA , 2005 ."
    },
    "sample_194": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Cambridge ,",
        "sentence": "Cambridge , MA , 1990 ."
    },
    "sample_195": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", MA ,",
        "sentence": "Cambridge , MA , 1990 ."
    },
    "sample_196": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Cambridge ,",
        "sentence": "Cambridge , MA , 1990 ."
    },
    "sample_197": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", MA ,",
        "sentence": "Cambridge , MA , 1990 ."
    },
    "sample_198": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Cambridge ,",
        "sentence": "Cambridge , MA , 1990 ."
    },
    "sample_199": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", MA ,",
        "sentence": "Cambridge , MA , 1990 ."
    },
    "sample_200": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Cambridge ,",
        "sentence": "Cambridge , MA , 2005 ."
    },
    "sample_201": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", MA ,",
        "sentence": "Cambridge , MA , 2005 ."
    },
    "sample_202": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "consult Special Collections <UNK>",
        "sentence": "Please consult Special Collections"
    },
    "sample_203": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Barcelona ,",
        "sentence": "Barcelona , 1993 ; Munchen , K.G. Saur , 1995 ."
    },
    "sample_204": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "; Munchen ,",
        "sentence": "Barcelona , 1993 ; Munchen , K.G. Saur , 1995 ."
    },
    "sample_205": {
        "gr": [],
        "pred": [],
        "overlap": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "mention": "Two Americans :",
        "sentence": "The Making of Two Americans : European"
    },
    "sample_206": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "PER"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Henry Hobson Richardson <UNK>",
        "sentence": "Traditions and Practices expressed in the Henry Hobson Richardson"
    },
    "sample_207": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "of Harvard University 's",
        "sentence": "and Eleanor Raymond Collections of Harvard University 's Graduate School of Design \" , Mary F. Daniels ."
    },
    "sample_208": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "'s Graduate School of Design \"",
        "sentence": "and Eleanor Raymond Collections of Harvard University 's Graduate School of Design \" , Mary F. Daniels ."
    },
    "sample_209": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", New York ,",
        "sentence": "Confederation of Architectural Museums , New York , 1998 ."
    },
    "sample_210": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Cambridge ,",
        "sentence": "<UNK> , Harvard Review of Latin America , Cambridge , 2003 ."
    },
    "sample_211": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Buenos Aires :",
        "sentence": "Buenos Aires : Through the Architectural Archive of Jorge Ferrari Hardoy \" ,"
    },
    "sample_212": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Cambridge ,",
        "sentence": "<UNK> , Harvard Review of Latin America , Cambridge , 2003 ."
    },
    "sample_213": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "'s Correspondence Courses :",
        "sentence": "Jaqueline Tyrwhitt 's Correspondence Courses : Town Planning in the Trenches \" ,"
    },
    "sample_214": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Trenches \"",
        "sentence": "Jaqueline Tyrwhitt 's Correspondence Courses : Town Planning in the Trenches \" ,"
    },
    "sample_215": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Vancouver ,",
        "sentence": "Presented at the Society of Architectural Historians Annual Meeting , Vancouver , April 2005 ."
    },
    "sample_216": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Digital !",
        "sentence": "Access and Preservation of Landscape Architecture Collections - in Digital ! \""
    },
    "sample_217": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "/ United States ,",
        "sentence": "Presented at the International Confederation of Architectural Museums / United States , Philadelphia , October 2009 ."
    },
    "sample_218": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Philadelphia ,",
        "sentence": "Presented at the International Confederation of Architectural Museums / United States , Philadelphia , October 2009 ."
    },
    "sample_219": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "ORG"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "the Allied Forces \"",
        "sentence": "Jaqueline Tyrwhitt 's Correspondence Courses for Members of the Allied Forces \" ,"
    },
    "sample_220": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Italy ,",
        "sentence": "Presented at War Perspectives Conference , Politecnico di Milano , Italy , January 2010 ."
    },
    "sample_221": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "<UNK> Buenos Aires :",
        "sentence": "Buenos Aires : La Ciudad Frente al Rio \" ,"
    },
    "sample_222": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Chicago <UNK>",
        "sentence": "Presented at the Society of Architectural Historians Annual Meeting , Chicago"
    },
    "sample_223": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Peru ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_224": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", LaSalle ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_225": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Ottawa ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_226": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Streator ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_227": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Mendota ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_228": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Princeton ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_229": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Spring Valley ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_230": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", De Pue ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_231": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Earlville ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_232": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Granville ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_233": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Ladd ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_234": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Marseilles ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_235": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Oglesby ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_236": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Seneca ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_237": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Sheridan ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_238": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Walnut ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_239": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Wenona ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_240": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Wyanet ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_241": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Dalzell ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_242": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Grand Ridge ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_243": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Hennepin ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_244": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", LaMoille ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_245": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Leland ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_246": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Naplate ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_247": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Ohio ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_248": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Utica ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_249": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Sheffield ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_250": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Tiskilwa ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_251": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Tonica <UNK>",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_252": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Peru ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_253": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", LaSalle ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_254": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Ottawa ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_255": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Streator ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_256": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Mendota ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_257": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Princeton ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_258": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Spring Valley ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_259": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", De Pue ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_260": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Earlville ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_261": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Granville ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_262": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Ladd ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_263": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Marseilles ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_264": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Oglesby ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_265": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Seneca ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_266": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Sheridan ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_267": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Walnut ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_268": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Wenona ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_269": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Wyanet ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_270": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Dalzell ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_271": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Grand Ridge ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_272": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Hennepin ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_273": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", LaMoille ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_274": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Leland ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_275": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Naplate ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_276": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Ohio ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_277": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Utica ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_278": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Sheffield ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_279": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Tiskilwa ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_280": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Tonica <UNK>",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_281": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Peru ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_282": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", LaSalle ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_283": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Ottawa ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_284": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Streator ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_285": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Mendota ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_286": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Princeton ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_287": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Spring Valley ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_288": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", De Pue ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_289": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Earlville ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_290": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Granville ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_291": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Ladd ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_292": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Marseilles ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_293": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Oglesby ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_294": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Seneca ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_295": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Sheridan ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_296": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Walnut ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_297": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Wenona ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_298": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Wyanet ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_299": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Dalzell ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_300": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Grand Ridge ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_301": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Hennepin ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_302": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", LaMoille ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_303": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Leland ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_304": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Naplate ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_305": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Ohio ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_306": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Utica ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_307": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Sheffield ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_308": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Tiskilwa ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_309": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Tonica <UNK>",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_310": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": "in Peru ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_311": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", LaSalle ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_312": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Ottawa ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_313": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Streator ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_314": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Mendota ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_315": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Princeton ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_316": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Spring Valley ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_317": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", De Pue ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_318": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Earlville ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_319": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Granville ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_320": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
        "mention": ", Ladd ,",
        "sentence": "Connecting Point Computer Center providing solutions for you in Peru , LaSalle , Ottawa , Streator , Mendota , Princeton , Spring Valley , De Pue , Earlville , Granville"
    },
    "sample_321": {
        "gr": [
            "MISC"
        ],
        "pred": [
            "LOC"
        ],
        "overlap": [],
